Hey, what's up?
How's everybody?
Oh, I actually didn't pull... hold on, I didn't pull you up here.
There we go.
Now I can see.
Oi!
What's up, Bapid Raven Warrior, Frank, Liminal Roar.
I see Dr. Mother in there, and Reef, Yujiri, all the usual suspects.
Good to see you.
How you doing?
Crack open that cold one!
For sure.
Damn right.
So, I wanted to do something special for today, but I didn't have time to set it up, but I'm gonna do it next time, which is...
Someone on the YouTube comments had a great idea.
And his name was MagnificentXXBastard, just in case you're here watching.
Thank you for the suggestion.
I'm gonna try and have an overlay, similar to what I did with Tunic, where I can have my notes and I can draw a sort of a map of the world as I know it.
I think it could be really fun to sort of fill out that map and draw a nice map, you know?
And we could combine it.
I think that would be really cool.
I'm gonna try and set that up for next time, because that's actually one of the things, you know?
Keeping notes of everything in this game is gonna help me immensely, so that would be unbelievably cool.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to doing that.
I just need to set it up correctly, I haven't done that yet.
But thank you, MagnificentBastard on YouTube for suggesting that.
On the next topic of things... Transtar North and Earth Disaster... No, wait, wrong notes, hold on.
This is for that other game.
That was a joke.
I have a bunch of notes also already on my physical notebook.
I'm gonna transfer that over to the on-screen notes for next time as well.
Okay.
I still have a bunch of things I wanna do.
Let me just rhyme up some of them.
I wanna go to the ocean hut again, because there's a markings of a tablet on the wall.
And I mentioned this last time, but I never got to it because I kept dying.
Yeah, that happened.
We have a demon eye that produces platforms in the west.
I wanna try to go all the way up there and fuck shit up.
That's one of the things on my to-do list.
I also wanna go to the ancient laboratory, a place I haven't explored yet, but I've seen it.
And I've been scared of it.
But all of this obviously has to happen in sort of late game, so I need to get some good stuff going, which is what I was trying to do last time.
Then there's also a dark area to the west in the hemisphere that I wanna explore.
The only way so far I know how to explore that place is to have the light spell modifier on some of my other spells.
So I need to figure out some kind of way to do that.
And I'm excited for it.
So those are the main ones.
They're smaller ones, of course, too, but other than that, I related to the whole mystery with the one in the pond, one on the ledge, one under the sun, all that stuff.
Also very intriguing.
But those are the main ones right now, you know?
Yeah, so that's the goal for today.
That is the goal.
Let me quickly do that.
Click here, click there.
Bam, we're in.
Yep.
Can you promise me you'll pick glass cannon every time you see it?
Yeah, but no.
I feel like no on that one.
Maybe in the future, but so far, that thing scares me, okay?
I'm scared of that perk.
God, it feels good to have Neuter.
What a game.
I've been having an absolute blast with this game.
I gotta say, I did not expect to have as much fun with this for this extended amount of time.
You know, it's just, it has such a high replay value.
It feels good, man.
Feels good to be a G, that's for sure.
Yep.
Thank you, Yuduri.
Okay, let's see.
I'm gonna close you guys down.
You know, the drill.
I'm just gonna sit here, sip my coke, play the game, and have some fun.
Ah, man, does it feel good.
Happy Sunday, everybody.
Continue?
Wait, where was I?
As far as I know, I just started a new run.
I didn't do anything yet.
Yes, exactly.
Okay.
Beautiful.
Let's see.
The name of the game, of course, is to play slow, meticulous, and precise.
All that good jazz.
Wait, I have dynamites.
I just broke a lamp.
I'm so sorry.
I'm gonna go up here.
Boink.
Because we are getting that HP.
Yes, sir.
What the fuck is that?
Huh?
What's happening here?
Why, why is, why is there... Okay.
Kind of want to blow it up now to see what happens.
Wait, what is that?
Stop moving the screen.
What is that behind there?
Ah, never mind.
I thought there was something in the earth.
Weird.
Okay.
Just wasted a little bit of dynamite.
That's okay, though.
Oh, man.
One hit?
Am I a god or what?
Amazing.
You can even grab that.
I cannot grab that.
That was my test.
I'm not getting that.
Actually, I am.
A hundred gold, man.
It's not that much.
I can grab it down here.
Definitely.
I am curious also about this roar every time I pick up one of these orbs.
And it must be an important thing because why would it be part of the UI?
You know, the UI is pretty minimal in this game.
We have health, we have levitation, we have mana, money, and then this is showing as well.
Like, why is that so important?
To be shown on the UI among all the other major indicators?
Makes me think something big is going on with that.
Something important.
Decent starter wand?
I like it.
A wand!
The hair in the back of your neck stands up.
Okay, so there's a little ghost symbol on it.
I'm not sure exactly what it means.
Maybe I'm just being haunted by a ghost somehow.
Ooh.
Yo.
That's a great wand.
Thank you very much.
No.
Oh, also, berserkium is what I have.
Okay.
You know what?
I'm going to drink it.
Just a bit.
Have that crit.
Maybe I should have saved it for a bit of a harder enemy.
When I see a big guy, you know, I can fuck him up.
That's already sort of a dead end.
That's interesting.
What is that?
That's not a rock.
That's a gravestone.
But I guess they are made of rocks, so.
Right.
Never mind.
Mm-hmm.
We are going berserk today.
Berserkium or the wind.
I wonder how much it actually does.
A berserk curse.
Wait, why is it called berserk curse?
Wait a minute.
Is that different from...
huh.
That's weird.
Okay, I'm not quite sure what's up with that.
A broken wand!
I'm gonna bring that to you-know-what place.
Honestly, that's one of the biggest secrets I found.
Or at least it feels that way.
I felt so cool when I found that out, man.
God damn.
Because those broken wands have been messing with my head for so long.
So if I see something else that's broken, maybe I can bring that too.
Repair all the things.
Someone's throwing dynamite?
Oil floats on water?
No surprise there.
Man, what a weird level.
What's going on here?
It's weirdly empty, isn't it?
More flammable.
I'm not actually sure, like, statistically what that means in numbers.
Maybe the fire just never won't go out.
Or it won't go out as long as I have that status, you know?
Whereas if you don't have oil status, the flame will go out naturally over time.
Maybe it's just easier to catch fire.
It's also a possibility.
Hemis.
Our first Hemis of the day.
I was about to say it feels good, man, but it also feels bad to slay them.
They are my homies.
I'm on fire already.
And I have no water.
The circum won't do the trick, unfortunately.
We have to endure this fire.
Maybe if I go up here?
No.
Shit, I am on fire.
Find some... Yeah, I know.
Why will this not stop?
Stop!
Jesus!
Man, that burned for a long time.
Rip gold.
Just do this.
Be careful here.
There we go.
Okay, so we lost a lot of HP there.
Not the greatest start.
Lava potion!
No, thank you, man.
Maybe I'll throw it at someone.
See, look at this.
That's not a rock.
That's a statue of someone.
Oh, oh no.
Oh, he died quick.
Weird.
Actually, I need blood or water.
Both of them will do.
Not a whiskey, though.
It's like the opposite of what I want in my cup.
Hey, you there.
Don't throw it over here, because I'm filled with oil.
Oh, is that what... Okay, I think this is what that means with the air feels haunting or something or whatever it said.
Oh, speaking of that.
By the way, I went back in the recording to check out the thing that I missed.
Remember when I was tripping balls?
There was a text that I missed.
I actually checked it out and wrote it down.
Listen.
It said, you feel something has changed.
You hear the word copper echoing and shifting in colors.
And then I died right after.
So I definitely want to explore that as well.
That's one of the things I also want to do today.
Figure out what the hell that means.
Why is copper linked to tripping balls?
You know?
Very intriguing stuff, I gotta say.
Why are these hammers glowing like that?
The hell?
Glowing him?
What's that?
Oh, this is the Kivaskivi.
And a wand.
Also, if I got to use my new wand, I found.
Look at all these gravestones.
Oh, is that because of the ghost?
That makes sense to me.
Bombs!
That's not bad.
That's really nice.
Oink.
So I wonder if there's anything I can do with these ghosts.
Other than kill them, I mean.
And I need to find water.
I really need to find water.
Now that we have a bunch of bombs and dynamite, probably we can just chill a little bit here.
Seems like these guys can't shoot straight up.
That's something I've noticed.
Sick shot.
That guy has a bunch of HP.
Definitely, that's how we do it here.
Oh, you know what?
I can just take this blood.
Oh, I just drank oil, I think.
Whoops.
Need to drink it.
Is there an easier way to... What is this again?
Circum plus blood plus oil.
Let's drink it.
Drink it all.
Become sick.
Am I...
I'm taking damage!
Oh, I'm fine now.
I think I drank way too much just then.
I don't want to mix the oil here.
I just want blood.
Come on, fill me up with blood.
Just need some kind of liquid.
That's too shallow for me.
We can use our bombs here.
Aha!
Look!
Look, there's a ghost following him!
What is going on?
Oh, that guy... Wait, does he have a... I'm so confused.
Whatever.
Grab the blood.
Speaking of blood, I had vampirism last time and oh boy, was that cool.
If I find that again, I'm taking it.
That was actually insane.
I didn't... It didn't last very long because I didn't have that great once, but that's fine.
Next time I will.
Nice!
Hey!
Barney!
You gonna... I knew... You see that little piece there?
That's why I didn't throw dynamite.
I knew it was gonna bounce off and hit me instead.
Whoa!
Close one.
That guy's scary.
Let's be really careful here.
That's how we do it.
Taking care... Is that... Yeah.
Okay, nothing to be scared of.
Look at all these gravestones.
What happens if I destroy the gravestones?
Let's try it.
It's all ghosty in here, right?
Something's going on.
Nothing.
Okay, well I had to try it.
Maybe I need to bring the gravestone somewhere.
What if I bring a gravestone to the... To the floating island above the mountain?
The snowy peak?
Will I be rewarded for my curiosity?
In some way or fashion?
Don't know what just happened there.
Collapsed mines!
What the... Another one of these!
Damn, dude!
Drain it!
Oh, we gotta be really careful!
Holy shit!
Yeah, I don't wanna... Yeah, we gotta be real careful here.
That dude is... Shooting things!
He's right below me.
I think I hit him a bunch.
Hey, you like that?
He died?
Yeah!
Nice!
Actually, a bunch of water there I could take.
Let me take it.
Why is it green?
Peat plus water plus swamp.
Yikes.
That's a nasty combination.
Peat is like some kind of soily water, I think.
I looked it up once.
Oops.
Wow, sick shot!
Another Barney?
Copper.
Okay, so copper is kind of linked to mushrooms somehow.
They also are kind of curious, right?
They look very weird in the world compared to everything else.
There's something going on with the copper.
If I find mushrooms, I will be tripping on that, boy.
We're gonna go on a trip together to outer space.
That's a biggie.
What should I use?
Probably just a saw blade here.
I gotta be careful because they can hurt me.
Nice!
That was sweet!
Not going for that.
Or am I?
Nah.
I'm still not entirely trusting of this flammable gas, you know?
Exactly.
What happens to flammable gas?
It burns.
So when you stand near it, there's a chance you're gonna get fucked, basically.
Yeah, it catches fire.
What's that?
Another Kivaskivi?
Is that a mushroom?
No, it's not.
I can't eat it.
It is not a mushroom.
That takes too long, doesn't it?
I'm gonna blow it.
Please don't burn.
Nice.
Boink.
Sick.
Now we grab some more water.
Good!
So I wonder, so now it's 30% peat, right?
If I just stay in the water, will it replace it?
It will not, okay.
So I have to MC it completely first.
I don't know if peat is bad, but look at that.
You don't want to be drinking that shit.
That's terrible.
There we go.
Pure water.
Now I fill it.
But don't go all the way down because that will take some blood.
Is that good?
1% blood.
That's fine with me.
We are now safe against burning, sort of.
More safe than we were before.
Let's just say that.
Worm pheromone.
You know what?
I will throw... Ooh, let's be careful with the lava potion.
How am I gonna safely dispose of that?
That's a legitimate concern.
I could put it beneath my feet, but I'm just still afraid of it breaking somehow.
I don't trust it.
You know what I mean?
Let's just throw it.
Get rid of it.
That has now safely been disposed of.
Okay, let's continue on.
I can never get enough of just exploring these caverns.
Is that weird?
Am I just easily entertained?
What's happening here?
Why is this so infinitely entertaining?
I don't understand.
It's the RNG element of it.
It's the same thing that Minecraft had, right?
Where you go into a cavern and you never know what you're gonna find.
Look at that!
A bunch of copper!
Just sitting in a pile.
What is going on, man?
Shotgun man up there?
Kinda wanna get up there?
Let's do it.
Hot bird!
O2!
HA!
Okay, I can breathe.
I can breathe.
That was scary.
I thought I was gonna die.
I like that there's an actual O2 meter when you're in the coal, man.
You can get buried in that shit.
That's a real death.
Shit!
I panicked hard just now.
I'm sorry.
Ah, dude.
This game.
This is the spot!
This is it.
This is where there's a bunch of darkness.
So when we find a light source, we gotta come back here.
We have 360 money.
Kinda a nice number.
That's one rotation.
We're doing it in degrees.
Uh...
Go up here.
Did I... Wait a minute.
I feel like I've discovered most things over here.
Let's go to the right.
New path!
I keep forgetting I can duck.
But when you duck, you also eat.
What's that?
Can I eat this?
Dude, I wanna try and eat everything now.
You know?
Just me eating that shit last time was like... blowing my mind.
We should be eating more things.
Hamis.
Sick, man.
The sniper?
Nice.
Oh, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit.
Uh, for that guy, we're gonna need... water.
Uh, hmm, wait a minute.
What if we do it like this?
Watch.
Huh!
Ya bi-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
Yeah!
I love the way they bounce around.
Those saw blades.
Actually amazing.
Too much fire, though.
That gold is tasty.
Don't take it, don't take it, don't take it.
Play it safe.
Don't be an idiot.
Levitation.
Uh, maybe I want that more than worm pheromone.
Okay.
Anything gonna kill me up here?
A wand!
Nice.
Look at that!
Another gravestone.
And it looks weird.
I mean, it's very hard to see what's on it, because it's very pixelated, but...
Definitely had some kind of symbol on it.
Shiny orb!
That is the thing that gives gold when you kick it, but then when you kick it too much, it explodes.
Um...
Let's bomb it.
Actually, let's get in here with a bomb anyway and see if we can... excavate that in the process.
I think it sort of worked.
It's gonna burn through.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not bad.
Oh no, Hamis, I'm so sorry!
Hamis burned alive.
Oh!
Magic arrow!
That is a sick weapon, actually.
Ten damage.
I mean, I'm soon out of bombs anyway, and this wand is not anything amazing.
So, let's use a bomb and come back and grab this.
That's what I'm thinking.
Oh, I could've... I could've gone up here.
Okay.
Get rid of that fire for me.
Man, the fire in this game burns eternal.
It's weird.
It just never stops.
Oil potion?
Wait a minute, look at this!
Doesn't that look suspicious?
Do we need to bring something on top of this?
Uh...
Since the oil is here, let's try it.
Let's put levitation down gently.
Grab that, and we're gonna try and put oil on that.
Or just, like, place it on it.
I feel like something's going on there.
I have a hunch, okay?
I have this feeling.
Chili egg?
Oh, maybe it's that one.
Or maybe keep us... I'm overthinking this.
Remember last time we had the whole oil barrel thing?
That was, like, a secret we found.
Um...
Okay.
What if we put this?
Oh, wait, this is fiery?
Let's be careful.
Uh, yeah, no, let's not do that.
No, I don't think there's anything there.
I changed my mind.
It's not obvious enough, you know what I mean?
The last time we saw sort of a secret thing, it was kind of obvious.
That was a great shot just now.
I'm proud of myself of that one.
What do we got here?
Chaotic polymorphine?
Maybe I want that more in oil.
I really like the chaotic polymorphine.
It's nice.
Look, there's a ghost following that around.
Rotten meat.
Okay.
I was stuck for a second there.
Got a little bit hairy.
I saw another one over here.
Is that toxic rock?
Why is that toxic?
What if I put water on it?
Nothing happens.
What if I put this on it?
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Uh-oh!
I'm in a bad spot here.
Come here!
Come here, buddy.
Shit.
I was trying to hit him in the face with that.
Okay.
Not bad.
Eh?
I hit him, I think.
Ah, he died, he died.
Beautiful.
Gold is gone, though.
Oh, that's electrified!
Ooh, that's bad.
Let's not mess with that.
That was one of those electrical kivaskibis over there.
Hey!
Nice dodge.
I feel like I'm getting better at dodging.
Just in general.
What's happening here?
Why is it all so fractured?
Split earth.
This is the spot with the boss that I still haven't killed.
Eh, hey!
Oh my god!
Puta!
Almost totally messed up my stuff.
Another weird gravestone statue.
Kind of look like those things from Worms.
When they die, you know, they always leave behind some sort of tombstone.
Looks like one of those you could have.
Usually you can customize that.
That's a wand, baby.
He has a ghost on him?
I don't know what it means.
It's following him.
Maybe he's being haunted.
Whatever that means.
He has like a haunted effect.
Dude, two wands?
Oh, but I can't dig anymore.
Ooh, that's a yikes.
Unless...
Let's be a little inventive here.
Oh, but that is steel, isn't it?
Shit.
Wait a minute.
We need some explosives here.
Unless the other one contains explosives and it's right next to it, maybe I can get lucky.
This in water.
And that is...
What is that?
Is that?
I don't know what this symbol is.
It's definitely a trap.
So, hmm...
I'm not sure how I feel about this.
What if we put this in the water?
Yeah!
Steam it all.
Steam it, steam it, steam it.
That's actually pretty cool.
They can do this.
And this one is not gonna burn me, right?
Oh, never mind.
It is gonna burn me, but not when I hold it.
Steam it up.
Man, I'm so good.
Let's see.
Um...
Yes, this one will dig.
What happened?
It is electricity.
No, wait, it's...
It's frost, I think.
No?
No, wait, that's electricity.
It's like very electricity feeling.
Okay, now we can dig through here and get that wand.
Yes, burn it up, baby.
Oh, that's another thing.
I can also just put fire on this wood.
Oh, I could have Kiva Skivit this.
Ah, whatever.
It meant I got this wand too, right?
So...
We get the bomb back.
Actually, a great wand too.
I definitely want that.
Thank you very much.
Very cool.
Now...
What if I put the Kiva Skivit in the lava?
Oh, shit, stop burning.
It's just going to sit there, huh?
Okay.
I think I have to try this last time as well, but what if I...
Is that being lavaed up?
Okay, they can chill out there.
That's cool.
In fact, wait a minute.
Chaotic polymorphine?
Wow!
It just sits on top of the lava, wow.
Okay.
Pretty cool.
I think it's time for us to leave.
We've done a lot here.
We've done a lot.
Get the fuck out of here.
Almost 500 bones to our name.
That's good.
Go!
Sweet.
We definitely heal up.
135.
A black hole!
Cool.
Oh, and a teleport!
Dude, multiple black holes!
That's great.
Let's see the perks.
Oh, yeah, it does this if I don't.
Stainless armor, that one is really good.
Never skip leg day.
And no more knockback.
I think I want this.
This is just pure damage reduction.
I am taking it.
I'm playing solid.
Now this one, what is that again?
Fireball orbit.
So that's similar to the saw blade orbit, I guess.
Instead, it's just fireballs this time.
Do the fireballs hurt me?
I don't remember.
I think they do.
That makes sense to me if they do.
Disc projectile, already have one of those.
Let's take all three black holes.
We can do some digging with that.
But it all depends on how fast it's going to be shot.
Sometimes when I shoot these, they just sort of stand still in front of me.
It doesn't make too much sense.
Like, I don't know why that happened.
But it did.
I think I want my...
Oh, teleport I need to buy.
That is great.
Immediately having a teleport.
Pretty sick.
Now this, fireball, should I go for that?
Maybe.
This is a non-shuffle.
And it's actually a decent wand.
This is a great wand.
Maybe I sawblade it up.
Let's see here.
Okay, can I shoot it faster?
I think it's a little faster.
Let's try this one.
Not bad at all.
And the first one is 0.8.
It's actually slower, isn't it?
Alright, put him here.
And then I want black holes.
And maybe I can throw in some TNT or bombs in here as well, because why not?
I guess I just need to remember which one I'm doing.
Maybe that's a bad idea actually.
Doing that will fuck me up.
I pretty much guarantee it.
At some point I'll think I'll be doing a black hole and I'll be doing a bomb instead and kill myself.
Mmm, I think I'm good here though.
Sparkly bombs.
Maybe fireballs, you know what?
Let's buy some fireballs.
And this one actually does digging.
I found that out last time.
So, maybe we... hmm...
Do I just go for this?
That is a good amount of damage.
50, right?
That's sick.
It's slow though, but it's good for difficult targets.
Then I go with the soblates as my primary killer.
I think I like this.
Yeah, I like this.
Let's do that.
And I... do I need to refresh?
No, let's not use the refresh.
We can save that.
Off we go, man!
This is a good start so far.
Let's remember, I have this.
The coal pits.
I have come for you.
Laid safe.
Fill up water, first of all.
Fill up that water bottle.
Ow!
Didn't mean to get hit there.
I guess I never mean to get hit.
Let me try the black hole.
Just to see how far it goes.
Let me try go through here.
Okay!
So that one actually goes a little distance.
Oh, nice!
Cool!
Hey!
Great!
Black hole, man, the digging on that is actually wild.
I understand why that one is not unlimited, even with the perk.
That would be a little crazy.
Good!
And then we have an explosive here.
We can probably blow that up, huh?
Because why not?
And then we leave.
Just leave mayhem and destruction in our wake.
Kind of want to throw out the chaotic polymorphine and just fill up another water bottle.
It's so useful.
Lamp.
It's a weird looking lamp.
What's going on in there?
Oh, not those guys.
Lava people.
That was a headshot.
Kind of want to check what these guys are called.
Where are they?
There.
Oh, no.
Pikutuli carpinin.
No, Pikutuli carpinin.
Yeah, okay, I got it.
Pikutuli carpinin.
I hate Pikutuli carpinin.
That is such a...
annoying enemy.
That blew up right in my face.
That was terrible, man.
It happens though.
But I got some extra max health for my efforts.
So that's something.
Let's see if this black hole kills people.
Hold on.
Give me that gold.
Okay, it's time.
I'm going to dig a hole through here and in the process try and combine it with killing someone.
Oh, it definitely sucked up that little barrel on the way up there and murdered one of them.
That's funny.
Just wait for all this to blow over.
What the hell is going on here?
I want to start some shit.
Let me through.
There's also a wand there.
Nice, so I have an axis here now.
I can go up here.
Should I be using this again?
Can I fireball this and get through?
I cannot, okay.
Boink!
Bro, the black hole is actually not...
I feel like I've been sleeping on that spell for a while.
I need to use it more.
Whoa!
Bloodlust!
I had that last time.
With a triplicate bolt.
I think I like it.
Oh, but the mana charge speed is atrocious.
Let me see how that works in action.
Oh, but I have to be careful.
These can damage me now, right?
Wait a minute.
I mean, it's definitely gonna...
It's definitely gonna do some damage.
Right?
And...
Although this wand is pretty nice.
Should I let go of that?
Is that a bad idea?
It only has two slots.
It's not that great.
And mana charge speed is actually not that great either.
I like this one.
Let's use this.
This is a great one.
There's a head.
Right there.
Do you see it?
It says meat.
Can I eat it?
I ate the head.
I am minimally satiated.
From the head.
Wow, that guy is in a very bad spot.
Let me tell you.
Watch.
It's gonna bounce off and hit this and kill him.
Oh, it doesn't bounce?
Oh, shit.
Hmm...
How am I gonna do this?
He's gonna die from these discs, right?
Huh?
Oh, there we go.
Yikes!
Water, water, water, water!
Goddamn, man.
What the hell happened there?
Oh, nice!
A heart!
Again, totally worth it, then.
Getting all this HP right here is a big deal.
I can dick with this.
I'm just so deathly afraid of those things bouncing off and hitting me, you know?
Nice.
Sick wand, actually.
Bunch of toxic sludge, we can clean it.
What?
How did he just die?
Oh, the saw blades hit him!
Amazing.
That was totally not intended.
Well, it was, but not in that instance.
You know what I mean.
This is a great wand.
Solid.
That's what that is.
And I can dig.
So here's this thing, though.
If I use my black hole...
Ooh!
A chest!
If I use my black hole through this, it's gonna eat up the chest, right?
It's actually sucking in everything.
That's the thing.
When I use the black hole, that's why it doesn't leave anything behind.
It just sucks it all in.
Let's be careful here.
Let's not hit the...
Oh, I can dig through this.
I don't need...
Yeah, I'm gonna use it.
Boink!
Oh, no!
It's...
I forgot that it also had a gravitational pull and it sucked in the chest itself.
I thought it was just gonna go right past.
Oh, whatever.
But I guess that was gold in there, so...
We're happy.
Got out in time, it seems.
That was a bit risky.
Oh, my God.
This is bad.
And I'm poisoned somehow.
85 HP?
That's a decent amount.
I still have five black holes left.
I do wonder if there is a way to make those black holes infinite.
That would be...
Insano style.
Hmm, okay.
I see lava, I'm scared.
Whoa!
Let me go right first.
Wait, gold?
What the fuck?
What happened here?
And why is the gold still there?
Sludge?
Look how fast that changes.
You just need a drop of water in there and that thing immediately switches.
Hand it over.
Yes!
600 gold, baby.
And I haven't even used the re-roll yet.
I should be more wary of using re-rolls.
I think I've been too trigger happy on that.
Because, I mean, if it doubles every time, that's gonna be an insane price.
Really quick.
That shit gets out of hand.
Whoa!
Damn, dude, that was a lot of goddamn money.
Wow.
That's a bunch of bombs.
I don't want it, though.
Hey.
Wow, that was close.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Dude, I just got like 500 gold out of that.
I have 1100 now.
The hell did I just kill?
Holy damn.
Why did I drop so much gold?
Okay.
That seems fine.
Let's keep going.
I need to be not stained, by the way, because I have this perk.
I'm not mindful enough of that.
I mean, it's very hard not to get stained.
In this game, you're pretty much stained a lot of the time, you know?
It's very hard to avoid.
But you can avoid it.
I guess if you're pro enough.
Which I am not.
Oh, I've been here.
I dug through that with my hole.
Volcanic sand!
Volcanic sand.
Do we have a volcano?
Oh.
What's up, guys?
How's it hanging?
Oh my god, it's terribly inaccurate.
But at close range, it's fine.
Nice.
Man, this slime is hard to get off.
It really stains the clothes, you know?
Like red wine.
I can get through here.
I was about to use a black hole, but then I thought better of it.
Wait a minute, I see people up there.
Look at that.
That's right.
Look at this stuff in the background here.
They were mining coal.
Those bastards.
But those are rocks, not coal.
Okay, that seems like a dead end there.
Oh, hit something.
Whoa.
Nice.
Oh, no, I'm stained.
Water me.
Oh, there we go, there we go.
Thank god.
Shit, wrong wand.
Sweet.
Oh, what's that?
Yo, what the fuck?
Why was he red?
It's like a new breed of...
Ghostbuster.
63 HP.
Ow.
Never mind.
49.
I mean, 44.
Oh my god.
Come on, come on, come on, stain it off.
What the hell am I...
Come on!
Why is it still on me?
I don't understand this.
Oh, no.
I think we gotta leave.
Yeah, I'm stained again.
We're going in, we're going in.
Fuck this.
Hurry!
Holy shit.
Goddamn.
220.
Not bad.
Okay.
What's that?
Gunpowder arc?
Yo!
Damn, that's sick.
Chunk of soil?
I am way too intrigued.
Teleporting cast.
Teleporting cast?
Have I had that?
Ping pong pa...
Dude.
Explosion of brimstone.
So many new spells!
What's here?
Duplication, greed, double the gold.
Peace with God...
Ooh.
Ho ho ho!
I kinda like this one.
You know what?
Let's not overthink things.
I'm making peace with the gods because I intend to leave this place so I can come back and change my wands.
And I have a black hole so I can easily make my way out of here.
Fuck yeah.
Summon wall?
That will bounce off projectiles, I guess?
Or make projectiles bounce off of it.
Explosion of thunder?
What the hell is all this, man?
Let's try this chunk of soil.
Don't soil yourself.
It's a material type.
I have never seen that.
In fact, it kinda looks like a Minecraft block.
Okay, I'm not...
I'm not...
Wait, I was shooting sawblades.
Don't shoot sawblades.
Don't panic.
There we go.
Just take it easy.
That actually just produces soil.
Straight up.
Why?
Okay.
Maybe it'll come in useful.
But that's pretty cool, I guess.
Then we have ping pong path.
I think it does exactly what it says.
Let's see how it looks, though.
It's a modifier.
Let's try it on this.
Ha!
Oh, that's fun.
So, wait a minute.
Will that always...
Will that go through enemies multiple times, I wonder?
Like, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop.
Because that would be wild.
What about this one?
Oh, that's scary, though, the way it comes towards me when I have the bloodlust on, isn't it?
Like...
That's scary.
Ping pong path.
That's cool.
What about this?
I think I had this one before.
What was it again?
Cast a spell from the...
Cast a spell from the closest enemy?
Oh!
Whoops.
Didn't mean to do that.
That is interesting.
So the...
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is this a static projectile?
Watch.
Uh, if we do...
This.
With that.
Oh, but wait.
I'm way too scared.
Ah, wait, this only does seven damage, though.
Wait, did I hurt myself?
I did hurt myself.
Okay.
Explosion of brimstone.
A fiery explosion.
What a weird thing.
Okay.
Explosion of thunder.
I guess it's exactly the same, but with thunder.
Maybe I don't want to do that right now, because I will kill myself.
And that's a fact.
Uh, what was this?
Circle of oil.
I think I want the glowing lance.
Here's the thing.
Will this ever bounce towards me in some way?
Because if this is ultimately completely safe, then I want to put it on this wand.
Because that will give it...
How much more?
Wait.
I need to drop this to see it.
There.
Thirty-three extra damage.
Oh, but you know what?
Maybe it's not... maybe it's a...
It's actually... I need to put something like this on this, then.
That is actually the best.
That's gonna do a sick amount of damage.
Right?
That's actually wild.
That's a good amount of damage right there.
Then again, this does five damage, but it shoots three of them.
So I wonder, is that three times thirty-three in total?
I mean, I can test it.
Wait a minute.
That should be like ninety-something damage.
So that does thirty-six.
This one should be doing like ninety-something.
Oh yeah, even more, I guess.
It's really good, it's really good.
That's a good one.
Oh!
People are exploding somewhere.
But the thing is, it's not very accurate, right?
That's the only thing.
So I think it's actually better to spark-bold it up.
On that one.
Maybe even try this on it.
Wait, why is it not doing the thing?
So when it hits something...
Oh, okay.
When it hits something, it just...
Oh, but wait a minute.
Oh, that's scary.
Ah, it still just sticks in it.
I thought it was going to go through.
If I can find a... Oh, a glowing lance though.
Ah, never mind.
I want to go with this.
Let's just try this for the heck of it.
That's a bit scary the way it bounces back and forth, but it is what it is.
That's going to be my main damage wand.
And then teleport wand, of course.
And then for my third wand...
I still want black holes here.
That's fine.
Maybe we do teleporting cast...
No, no, no.
No teleporting cast.
I don't like that at all.
Ah, glowing lance maybe?
That was 35 damage.
No, this one is just better.
Bombs, I guess?
I mean...
Yeah?
And then when bombs are gone, we pollen?
Sure.
Why not?
Summon wall.
Let's try that.
Summon is a short-lived obstacle.
This thing will not damage me, right?
Not like the horizontal bullshit that I summoned once and I killed myself with it.
You know what?
I like it.
That's dope.
In fact, look at the way...
Oh, I'm stuck now.
Don't do it on top of yourself.
And you can't move.
It looks exactly like the effect you get...
when you use the demon eye.
And the platforms appear, remember?
That is the same animation.
I'm going with this.
Defense, offense, utility, and digging.
Great.
I'm not going to take the refresh...
yet.
Oh, before we do anything, let's do this.
Damn right you look the other way, because we're pals now, baby.
Enter snowy depths...
Wait, remind myself, spark bolt.
Whoa!
Oh, wait a minute!
I fucked up!
We gotta go back, we gotta go back.
I don't like how this...
is on here, actually.
Because this needs to be... this needs to keep going.
This needs to keep going until it hits something.
I don't want it to stop midair and go back and forth.
There we go, that's better.
Okay, here we go, man.
Snowy depths time.
Who's shooting who?
Oh shit, okay, okay, I see,
I see.
Bam.
Doink!
Never has a spark bolt been so much damage per shot.
What I really need though for...
Oh, oh shit, get away from me.
I was about to say I need a chainsaw for this to make it shoot faster, but...
there's only two slots in this wand, so...
that's not gonna work.
And unfortunately the bloodlust is only limited to this wand.
Right in the tummy.
This is a great wand, it's super simple, it makes sense.
No bullshit.
It just works.
We don't have any water.
That's an oof.
You know what?
I'm gonna do the ultimate, the most responsible thing I've ever done...
in this game.
I'm going back up...
and grabbing the water.
I know.
It's unheard of.
Oh man, this recharge on the teleport is terrible?
Maybe I'll change it with the wand...
or with the...
wall spell.
Let me change these up.
Go like that.
There we go.
And then...
water.
Grab the water.
Look at that.
I'm proud of myself.
Feels good.
Doesn't it kind of look like...
when you walk with your character that one of his hands is holding his trousers up?
As if you know how girls, when they have a dress on and they walk outside...
they always use their hands to hold up the dress to not let it get dirty.
It looks like he's doing that when I walk around.
Look, doesn't it look like he's sort of holding up the dress to not let it get dirty?
I've always gotten that impression from this animation.
Because you can't see his hand, you know?
Where is his hand?
It's doing things.
Somewhere where you can't see it.
Let's go.
Water that.
What?
I hear fireworks.
Oh!
That guy's scary.
Oh, he killed him for me!
Lovely.
Damn, son.
It's basically the Frost version of the fire guy in the... in the hemisphere.
Oh my god, come on.
Shit!
They have a... they have some HP here.
Got him.
Oh, that guy though, he's electric.
Nice.
That works.
Argh, can't move!
Brother!
My goodness!
That hurt a lot, man!
He came out of nowhere...
to fuck up my shit.
And old boys, my shit fucked.
Okay, I know where I am.
Yikes!
Nice.
Uh, let's wait for all this bullshit to subside.
Come on, particles, move!
That gold?
Oh, it was.
Sheed.
Uh, I could use...
No.
Got him!
Hit him with the crit there.
Why is the wind so aggressive here?
Oh, we got a machine gun.
He's off screen somewhere, that's annoying.
Maybe I can surprise him a little bit.
Oh my goodness.
Man, those guys are gonna be the end of me.
Ah, this is a bad spot.
Shh!
Oh, you know what?
Oh, whoa, whoa.
It has trouble tracking me.
Ah, so when you go all around them like that, they actually can't keep up with their tracking.
That's good so it doesn't want.
Dropper bolts?
Burning trail?
Let me try it.
So it shoots burning trail with...
Oh, yikes, that's way too scary.
Nope.
Not doing that.
Now there's a guy down here that scares me.
Where is he?
Hey, hey.
Okay, dude.
Something wrong with the audio?
Sounds weird.
Maybe not.
Where's the electric guy?
I feel like I hear him.
There he is.
Jesus!
Oh!
These guys are scary when you cannot one-shot them, man.
So, if my calculations are correct, based on the damage we do, they have like 300-something HP.
So you need to have that amount to reliably kill these dudes.
Let's grab some more water.
Oh, we have full water.
Ooh, double no.
Don't like it.
Nope.
Not enjoying that one.
Or though, am I enjoying it?
Hold on.
Maybe I enjoy it more than the wall.
Yeah, fuck the wall.
That's electric.
That's bad.
Let's not step in that.
By the way, what are those guys called?
That fucked me up here.
Is it that guy?
Guku?
And we have Pakasuku and Eldari.
And Stendari.
Stendari?
They're all sort of related, I think.
Ouch!
Oh my god, don't be near the water!
I'll kill him, please!
Ah, there we go.
Ah, this is over, boys.
18 HP?
Oh my god.
Get the fuck out of here.
Oh, shit.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
We gotta get to a portal immediately.
Portal time?
Where are you?
Blood myself up.
There we go!
But there's an enemy.
I hit him once.
Don't shoot me.
Shit!
Bye-bye.
That was scary, dude.
Holy...
Let's go.
Just get through it, man.
Yep.
Heal up.
Very good.
Okay, what do we got here?
I like the lightning bolt.
I like it a lot.
That seems promising.
Let's check the perks.
Teleportitis.
You take 20% less damage to teleport every time.
See, that seems horrible.
Contact damage?
Enemies near you take damage.
The damage is higher the lower your health gets.
No.
I don't like any of these.
We're gonna spend a re-roll.
Permanent shield?
Wait, what?
What does that mean?
Mournful spirit.
Dying creatures leave behind a spirit that deals the damage in a small area.
Are these the kind of spirits that were already following creatures that I saw?
Salt powders.
I think I want to try this.
What does that mean?
You gain a small...
Okay, I see it.
What am I...
Permanent shield?
What does that mean?
Flat damage reduction?
Or it's not just gonna absorb.
Okay, wait a minute.
Lightning bolt.
Accelerating shot.
Flamethrower.
Magic arrow with timer.
Actually...
Buy this one first.
Because that's a surefire spell right there to have.
I want to try this real quick.
If I put the timer here...
What does this look like?
How much damage does that do?
It's not that much.
I mean, I'm gonna go with my one and only.
The lightning bolt.
My good old pal.
That is consistent damage right there.
Love it.
Absolutely love it.
Oh, but this is...
This can already kill me.
So what's the difference between having this on...
This a nut on here?
Oh, the recharge speed is terrible.
Bro, the audio is bugging again.
You hear that?
Hold on, I'm gonna restart the game.
Because I had this happen once.
And it kind of sucked.
I want the audio.
Okay.
Let's see.
Is it better?
Yeah, we're back.
Perfect.
I wonder what causes that.
Thundercloud...
I mean, I don't have money for any of this anyway now.
All right.
Is it time?
Oh, wait a minute.
We have floating arc.
Wait a sec.
I forgot that we had the double.
Can we do something with it?
Maybe I...
Maybe not right now.
Teleporting casts.
Yeah, what if I...
Hello?
Oh, okay.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't like that.
Sometimes it's closer to me.
Sometimes it's not.
That seems weirdly random.
That's bad.
Don't do it, people.
Now, this could be cool.
Dude, kind of wish there was a trigger on that instead.
That's actually a really...
cool way to do that.
Actually, it's not.
Because if you accidentally hit someone in close range, it will deploy in close range.
But I guess that's the same without.
Let's make a difference.
I like this, I think.
Yeah, that's good.
That's good.
Now, in this one down here, let's put some bombs.
And what else have we...
Ah, that's fine.
Maybe this one.
Why not?
Just have a rant.
It's like a digging thing.
It's a digging thing.
And now?
Let me try and absorb this guy.
Come here.
Didn't hurt him.
It didn't hurt him at all.
Oh, I didn't even see you there, man.
What the hell?
Alright, we're back in a easy base.
Fuck yeah.
Man, the lightning strike is fantastic.
I have a new fear of these tanks.
I gotta be honest, those tanks right there, they...
They scare me.
How about we do this?
That's for you.
Then we blow that shit up.
What a death.
That guy had a really bad day.
We blow them up now.
That's the new rule.
We blow those fuckers up.
Except this is annoying.
I don't like the freezing vapor.
That makes me very unhappy.
There's another tank.
I guess we just wait for it to go away.
They do... it does kind of dissolve after time.
Oh my god.
There's a whole congregation of people.
Man, the recoil on this.
Sweet.
Ah!
What the fuck?
I hit that thing instead and electrocuted myself.
I was gonna shoot this?
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
New lesson learned here.
Don't fucking shoot this thing near anything that's metal.
I feel like I never had this problem last time I was using this extensively.
The hell is going on?
Okay, new rule.
I don't want to blow these up every time.
Because it's just gonna mess me up.
See, I'm scared now of using it.
Because there's bad frames and stuff.
Am I fine?
What if I shoot like that?
Yeah, that definitely electrocutes things.
Oh my god.
Electricity?
I need electricity resistance.
That's what I need.
Or maybe just don't stand on the surface, you know.
Maybe if I just float a little bit when I shoot.
I'm too scared.
I'm not going that way.
No, I'm not a pussy.
Let's go.
Also, why is my wand black?
You see that?
My wand is black.
Huh?
What did I do?
What's going on there?
Okay, we're fine.
I forget I have teleport.
Jesus!
I feel like I should not be afraid of the electricity.
I feel like the more afraid I am, the worse it gets.
You know, it's like, don't be afraid of the cooking knife.
Just use it.
Don't be afraid of it.
Fucking do it.
You know what I mean?
The hesitation is the thing that's gonna kill me at some point.
What is my second... That's that one, right?
Wow, it didn't even die.
What the...
God damn.
Almost shot me in the face.
I think I should be looking for an exit.
But kind of want to find some wands.
Ah!
I have a broken wand.
I will be taking that if I can find it to that place.
How am I gonna do this?
You can't see me, right?
No, no, no.
Why can't I shoot that?
Oh, I electrocuted that guy.
That's actually a legit strategy.
Damn.
Aww.
That was a waste of a black hole.
Oh wait, that's way too dangerous.
What the fuck am I doing?
Ah!
Like, I have the bare minimum of wands right now.
Let me go this way instead.
Oh, it's a dead end.
Shit.
I guess I go here then.
Just go to dark areas.
Boink.
So, my immediate objective.
Whoops.
Find the anvil.
And then get the fuck out of here.
Wait, are those neon lights?
Are they having a party?
And I wasn't invited?
More.
Come on, guys.
Oh shit.
What the hell is going on?
Oh, it's the little pedal thingy exploding.
Oh, this is looking bad, guys.
Yeah.
It's looking real bad.
Come here.
There we go.
Next.
Yes.
See ya.
Question.
Will this break steel if I destroy that?
Let's test it.
Oh, I'm scared of these.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You know what?
Don't mess with propane tanks.
Bad idea.
There's so many of them, though.
And I really want to mess with them.
Don't go into water with that.
I almost made a crucial mistake.
Oh, right.
There's this.
Is that always here then, I wonder?
Spark bolt with trigger.
I want to put that on...
Oh, I was about to say lightning bolt, but then I don't think that's actually what I want, after all.
But I will take it, because that's a good one.
Okay.
Thank you.
Moving on.
Which one do I have on?
This one?
Okay.
Yeah, let's be careful here.
Can't get through there.
Back up we go.
I don't fit.
I'm so scared of these tanks.
You like tanks?
That's for you, sir.
Hey!
Oh!
My shield!
It works!
Oh my god, oh my god!
It totally absorbs...
Okay, I understand how this works now.
It's like, it absorbs one shot.
And then it comes back online.
That is frickin' awesome.
Nice.
Sweet stuff right there.
I'm loving this perk now.
That's a chest!
Um...
Let's get it.
And there's a one too!
Hell yeah!
Any enemies?
Come here.
I'm gonna clear the area here before I...
God damn!
What, what's that?
What's that?
Facing arc!
Makes a projectile fly much slower, but teleports short distances over its flight.
Huh!
Acid...
Acid cloud.
How about no on that one?
Um...
That's actually pretty intriguing.
I like that idea.
I don't know why I like it yet, but I like it, you know?
It's just nice.
Um...
Okay.
Guess I'll...
That's a big...
Hold on, if I put this on...
How big is it?
Ha!
It's actually the same size!
Wild.
Hold on, do I actually want this?
Instead of this?
I don't really...
I'm not...
attached to these spells at all.
You know what?
I think I want this, actually.
I'm taking this for now.
Yeah, what?
40 HP.
I gotta be real careful.
So I wanna get through here, because there's a chest.
There's some snow.
This thing is great for removing snow.
Yay!
Sweet!
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
Oh, how you doing, sir?
Oh, you want dance?
He's gonna fuck me later if I don't take care of him now.
He electrocuted.
Unfortunately, I can't get down here, because of the metal.
Or steel, I should say.
Go around down here, I see a path now.
No, I don't.
Oh, no, it's blocked, but I do have black holes.
I just remembered.
Doink!
Nice.
Another heart.
That's gonna explode, by the way.
Let's get in cover.
Come on, explode.
No, you want to.
Oh, that thing is burning.
Come on!
Is it really not?
There we go.
Oh, the heart fell.
Sweet!
Oh, shit.
We've got propane tanks, and they're wild.
I should really not stain myself right now.
No stain, and we get damage reduction.
Oh, I just absorbed the shot?
The whole gang is here.
Hey, people.
Yo-ho!
Bigger than I thought.
I see you.
Yep.
We also want some.
Yo, is this protecting me from falling fire?
Do we do a quick test?
The shield, I mean.
That would be amazing if that's the case.
Oh, shit.
I'm on fire, I'm on fire.
Shit.
29 HP.
We cannot be playing around.
There's a wand in there.
This is all metal.
Electrocute them.
There's so much gold, though.
He's still alive.
I had to grab it.
Let's see.
Plasma beam.
An instantaneous dangerous beam of light.
Venomous curse and a triple.
Maybe I want this more than that.
Yeah.
I will take that instead.
Thank you very much.
I see a bomb.
Let's explode it.
Just to be safe.
But see, now I've created another hazard, which is the fire, right?
So maybe it's not always a good idea to explode bombs.
Only if they clearly mess with my path, you know?
Otherwise, don't do it.
Whoa!
I totally absorbed the shot.
So it's not just a single shot.
I think it's a damaged threshold.
So when that threshold is reached, the shield disappears and reappears a short time after.
Oh.
That was a dead end.
Sweet.
Don't catch fire.
Oh, shit.
Let's just wait for that freezing vapor to get out of here.
Man, that burns forever, whatever that is.
Of course it dissipates when I say it.
Or point it out.
Get these out of here.
I have no more black holes.
I was tempted to just black hole my way through there.
Not the best idea.
Bye-bye.
I'm waiting for that.
No, I'm going to go here, actually.
And where is this anvil?
I wonder if it's always here or not.
It could be a randomized thing.
The levels are random, right?
Nice portal.
Sweet.
There we go.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Look at all that blood.
What the fuck?
Why is there so much...
Here we go, here we go, here we go, here it is happening.
Let's try it.
Let's see.
Concentrated explosion.
Limits the radius of a projectile's explosion heavily.
Orbiting arc.
Wait.
A projectile orbits the point of its...
I don't know about that one.
But I'll take it.
I think I like it.
The wand itself is actually pretty dope.
Look at that wand.
That is a dope ass wand.
Is that water electric?
I mean blood.
I'm going to go through.
Nice.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
We made it.
Despite everything, that was a tough one.
Let's...
Wait, what's that?
Oh, that's probably the bring the enemy to me spell.
Okay.
I see the perks.
I hear explosions over here.
Are people making their way in?
Extra health?
50% extra maximum health?
Projectile repulsion sector.
Projectiles that fly into a small sector in front of you get blown away.
Now that...
is actually something I'm curious about.
Maybe I want that.
I have another thought, though.
Maybe I will not take any of these perks.
Come back later when I have more HP and yoink this one.
Hmm?
50% if I can find more hearts in the Indian Terram.
Come back here, grab that.
That could be big.
Oh, that's digging.
Nice.
Actually a sick wand as well.
Dude, what?
These wands are sick?
Point...
This one is 0.12, 0.47.
Lot of mana.
Sick recharge speed, though.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, they're not as sick as this one.
This is a sick...
This is a great wand I have here.
Wow.
Let me get rid of these.
I don't think I want them.
Yet.
This one, maybe.
I don't think I want that, though.
Can we make something great happen, is the question.
Probably not.
Spark bolt with trigger to that one.
Always on imp...
Now, you know what?
I like the consistency of just the lightning bolt.
You know what you're gonna get, you know?
Let's see this one.
No.
What if I just do a bit of that?
The issue is, it's not fast enough.
If I was gonna do this, I need something fast.
Fast as fuck, boy.
How about we do something like that instead?
What is that gonna look like?
This is gonna shoot two spells.
This one and that one.
But this one is gonna shoot another spell when it collides.
And is that spell gonna be double spell?
Let's see.
Let's see the board.
One shot.
Oh wait, it also has the concentrated explosion.
Oh, wait a minute, concentrated explosion.
That could actually be pretty dope for this one, no?
Look how small it is!
And look how big it is here.
Ah, I guess it's sort of the same.
I can't really tell.
Anyway, let's try this.
So first it shoots the double.
Okay, so it doesn't actually do anything there.
But if I do this,
definitely higher DPS for sure.
So it shoots that one first, which is this.
And the next spell is that, which shoots...
Oh, I need to change these, I think.
And it shoots that one and two of these, because this one is gonna shoot that one the next time around.
I mean, it's kind of fast, I guess.
It's not amazing.
It's just damage, it's just simple as want.
But here's the thing, the castor lay is very small.
So if I just throw a bunch, maybe I will use these.
Hold on.
What if I just go a little nuts here?
Because I have a bunch of these.
Right?
Let's just see what this does.
Oh wait, do these ones damage me?
I'm not sure.
Let's see.
Wait, they don't.
I'm safe.
I'm safe!
I thought for sure these damaged me.
What the hell?
I've been thinking that for the longest time.
So that means...
I'm gonna...
What am I gonna do here?
Think.
This one, maybe.
How's that gonna look?
Why is it so slow, though?
Oh, because each of these adds a castor lay.
Ah, that's what's happening.
So the castor lay is actually quite high in the end.
So maybe there's a sweet spot.
You know?
Dum, dum, dum.
That's a little slower, isn't it?
That's even slower, so now we're actually being bottlenecked by recharge time.
Well...
I mean...
So if that doesn't hurt me, maybe I will try this.
Heh, heh.
That's fun.
That's actually really fun.
But it's not very precise.
It's only for very close quarters, I guess.
Orbiting ark, huh?
What if you make orbiting ark on...
Where is it?
Oh, I was gonna say the wall I have, but I don't have the wall anymore.
That would be fun.
Um...
Teleporting cast...
What else should I be doing?
I don't have an idea for any good wand here, I gotta be honest.
I think I'm just gonna stick to my lightning bolt as boring as that sounds.
Um...
Maybe I can put something here, because this one does have bloodlust.
Would be kind of a waste.
Maybe I do this on that one instead.
Oh wait, then these will damage me.
Let's not do that.
No.
Back this one goes.
I definitely want to recharge spells this time.
Get rid of this one.
I think I'm just gonna keep it simple.
Do I want this at all?
Explosion of...
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Can I make a sick sort of...
How much does this do?
45 damage.
Oh boy, this is not a modifier, unfortunately.
It's a static projectile.
Ah, dammit.
Dammit all.
I don't want it.
I don't want these either.
Don't think I want that either.
I'm gonna go all in on these for that wand.
But the thing is, we can come back later and do changes, right?
That's like the whole thing.
Gonna fill this one up.
We're gonna be shooting this green snot.
Alright, I think we're good.
We can always come back.
Let me recharge my spells...
and head the fuck out of here.
Actually, I could buy another wand.
Wait a minute.
I forgot about that.
I have enough money already.
Maybe I want this one for the digging.
How about we use that for now?
Uh...
Quadruple scatter.
No.
Wait, digging bolt.
A bolt that is ideal for...
What if...
I...
Wait, how did I do this last time, where I put the digging?
On...
Oh, it was with this one.
I can dig at a distance with this.
So what, so if I do this...
Okay, it's gonna take too long, though, to reach that point.
Let me go over here for now and deposit these, just so I can pick them up easily if I need to.
That should be digging now.
If I add a bunch of these, what happens then?
It's just gonna shoot the digging by itself, of course, because this one only grabs this one, right?
And then after this, these are just gonna be shot individually.
Okay, that makes sense.
Yup.
Yup, yup, yup.
Well, I think it's good to have these, no matter what.
Let me just put these over here for now.
Grab these back.
Maybe it doesn't make too much sense to grab all these, but...
I'm gonna put these up here.
What do I not want?
I don't want this.
Wait, what?
Something just shook the screen.
Alright, I think I'm good.
This one, though, needs to be teleported, of course.
Teleport, teleport, teleport...
Did I throw that away?
What the hell?
Wait.
Oh, wait, it's on this one, it's on this one.
So, quickly grab that, take the teleport, replace that one, honestly.
Throw that away.
Let me grab this wand again.
Whoops.
Grab this one here.
Use it instead of...
What do I not want?
Maybe I don't want the...
It pains me to say, but maybe the glowing lens goes away.
I don't want this wand.
I'm gonna keep this wand instead.
Boink!
There we go.
In fact, wait a minute, .10, .2?
400, 104?
Maybe that's better.
Hell yeah.
That seems to work good.
Let's move!
Grab the recharge, and then we're out of here.
288 HP, that's decent, man.
It's not bad.
And then when we come back later with more HP, we're gonna grab this extra health.
Let's make a hole.
Boop!
Damn right you looked the other way.
You don't want to mess with me.
Double spell.
Magic missile.
No.
That's a mine.
I think the shield is protecting me from falling fire.
Like the fire that falls from the roof.
Oh shit!
I don't like the spiders, man.
Not again.
Do I even have anything good to deal with it?
Oh my god, this shield is incredible.
There's a wand!
Ha!
What?
Accelerating shot, double spell, a bunch of fucking missiles.
Yo, this is insanity.
I think I will take it.
I'll come back.
Wait a minute, let me try this.
Hey, it didn't do anything.
Oh, it needs to be precise.
We need homing on that.
Oh, you were electrified!
Nasty.
Can I blow that up?
What's shooting that?
Oh, it's that thing!
Man, it has HP.
I think I want this more though.
Although that wand is kind of... No, it's shuffle.
Just shuffle wand.
We don't want that here.
We do no shuffle in this house.
Let me try this a bit.
It has some sweet recoil on it though, if I want to be flying somewhere.
This is my long range weapon.
It's not bad.
This stuns them as well.
Actually pretty useful.
I hate the growths.
Make me unhappy.
Okay.
Get up there.
You guys want this?
Oh no, I'm filled with this bullshit.
Water me, water me, water me.
He's shooting that malicious powder.
Come on, get it off of me!
I'm poisoned!
There.
Man, I'm losing way too much HP here.
It's not looking good.
It's really not.
I hate this little flower.
At least I'm getting good amounts of money.
That means I can get up there and grab some more wands if I need to.
It's raining fire.
From where though?
Uh oh.
Gee, stop it, stop it.
Ah!
There's too many of them.
Oh my god, what is going on?
They're fighting each other.
I'm burning.
I was too busy looking in the top left, I didn't even pay attention.
There's a wand over there.
Gotta check it out.
Sweet.
Oh, look at that.
Haha.
The hell?
Home bringer, yikes.
No thanks.
Although...
Oh!
That is actually a good modifier to have.
Maybe I will take that.
I'll take that and come back.
Just need to remember where I am.
Ah man, I really want that perk where I can tinker with wands everywhere.
Let's leave it for now.
I'll come back for that later.
So it's sort of similar to the top, let's remember that.
Close to the top and to the right of the entrance.
Top right.
Well not all the way right.
So the question is, should I be going down or explore more?
That is like the whole debate in my mind.
I think I want to explore, because we need to find HP.
That is the goal.
We want to get strong and buff, all that.
I think those two are the same thing, but you know.
The idea is there.
That's the wand I had before.
These things explode in a mess that I do not enjoy.
Aha!
A wand.
Double reduce spread!
I do like the reduce spread.
Oh wait a minute, something's going on.
I heard a shook.
Something's shaking.
This thing is bleeding that bullshit.
Uh oh.
I don't think he died, he got electrocuted.
Oh what the f- Frogs!
And something's shooting stuff.
Oh it's you!
You're shooting stuff.
It's bouncing off my shield!
That is fantastic.
This shield is amazing.
It may be one of my favorite perks so far actually.
I'm not saying it's the favorite, but it's definitely up there.
I think I want this.
I'm gonna go back now and...
deposit this.
Then I will come back for this.
So it's down and then that way up, okay.
The question is, where did I enter?
I think somewhere up here.
Yeah, it was close to here.
So it's just down.
Oh yes, right here!
Perfect, perfect, perfect.
Good!
Definitely keeping that and also that one.
We can throw that there.
This wand sucks though?
Actually it doesn't.
That's a decent wand too!
Why did so many great wands here?
Let me just throw it here.
Cool!
Then we go down...
explode that one.
And here it is.
Nice!
We're back.
Come on, give me some HP.
Why did all that fire come from?
Oh, that's a mine.
And a bomb.
Aww, dead end?
Shit.
Let me grab some water.
Cool!
It's going pretty well!
Despite my limited weaponry here.
I see you.
Eh, excuse me.
How are you not...
What the fuck?
There we go!
Finally.
Now, barren soil, can I?
Yes I can.
Oh wait, that's a spider isn't it?
I don't want to go in there.
I changed my mind, we're not going that way.
Although we just take a quick peek, quick peek.
Dude, I'm actually liking this magic bolt.
The shield is saving my ass.
It's absorbing so much.
Man, is this the place where those flying clouds are?
Because if this is the place, I'm out of here immediately.
Hello!
Oh no, don't hit me with that.
They shoot that bullshit.
Oh my, he has HP.
Spider, can I kill them reliably?
Oh, okay, thank God.
The mine bounced off my shield.
Fantastic.
Stop it.
I gotta say, this shield right here, it may be my favorite perk.
It's definitely tied with, well...
Oh, that was a mine.
Whoop.
It's tied with the Tinko with Wands perk for me.
All these legs flying everywhere.
What a violent explosion that produces.
That is a monster, I think?
Wait a minute, I can hit him from here.
What?
That's the wrong wand.
This is the wand I needed.
Fuck yeah.
So it seems, okay, new theory about the shield I have here.
I think the damage threshold is such that if I spell, below a certain damage hits it, then it will be repelled.
But if it's above that threshold, it goes through.
And when it goes through, or maybe it just breaks the shield in that case, and then it recharges.
Oh, another wand.
Let's fucking go, dude.
Ooh.
Um...
I don't like the bubble spark.
Holy mana charge speed.
Now that's a number I've never seen.
Holy shit.
And minus 14 on spread.
But it's shuffle.
That's bad.
We don't like that.
Wait, this contains a worm.
Kill the worm.
Jobs no money.
What a scam.
I was doing that purely for the money there.
Oh, oh.
Dude, that would have hit me.
What the hell is that?
That guy has a wand!
Come here, come here.
He spawns little babies.
Ha ha.
Sweet.
Let's see it.
Ooh.
Healing bolt.
That's the thing I can't figure out.
251 mana.
This is actually...
Oh, it's shuffle.
But I kind of want to take it just for these, because I want to do some more experiments with it.
There's got to be a way to use them on myself, right?
Maybe I'll come back for it?
No.
I'm taking it now, and I'm going back with it immediately, just like before.
So where is it?
It's like the air.
I'm going right...
and I'm going up.
Okay, so with the red plant here.
Red plant, left and down.
And then...
Ah, okay, so it's close to the surface.
I think the entrance is more to the right.
Somewhere over here-ish.
There it is!
Amazing.
That was quick.
Let me actually try it real quick.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Wait, it makes the projectile fly much slower.
Teleports short distances over its- Oh, but it's- Wait, this is shuffle!
So wait a minute.
Oh!
Did it...
Did it work?
Am I- Wait a minute.
I'm wasting a lot.
No.
I don't think that's working.
And although...
Hmm...
Can I...
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
I have an idea, I have an idea, I have an idea!
Watch this shit.
Uh, wait.
Did it heal me?
No, it didn't.
I healed myself!
Fuck yeah!
Now I just need to figure out how to do this even better.
I have an idea, I have an idea, I have an idea.
Watch this.
We're gonna be slowing it?
So that's a modifier, right?
This is a modifier?
That's a modifier.
Oh, that's a spell.
So watch this.
What?
Wha- Wha- Yay!
Oh wait, is it- Oh, is it maybe only one heal it does?
Once- Why is it so random?
Oh, it adds spread.
Protect health speed.
Wait a minute.
It adds spread.
Why is it so random?
Oh my god, it's so consistent!
Yo!
It's happening!
Look at this!
The heal is real!
Oh!
Look how many I have as well!
Oh my god!
Ugh, can I make it even better?
I wanna- I wanna- I want something that I can just do immediately.
Hold on, I actually have a bunch of spells here as well.
I have-
Uh, wait.
Wait, what else do I have here?
I have- Oh wait, I don't have a teleport on it?
Or is it there?
I have that one.
Maybe that- Dude.
Dude, wait a minute now!
Wait a minute!
Oh wait, I can't check if it heals.
Um, let me try with another one then.
Okay, so let's say I stand-
Wait, what?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
So that stops there, right?
But if I have this on...
It's like...
Weirdly random.
It floats above the- That's weird.
Huh...
Cast this- Dude!
No wait, no, no, no, nevermind, nevermind, nevermind, nevermind, nevermind, nevermind.
Uh, that's not good.
Orbiting maybe.
That could- That could work.
But I need to test it with the healing if it actually hits me.
Let me do one shot of this.
I don't know if that worked.
But dude!
Whatever.
I can heal.
I can heal!
That's the most important thing here.
That is so sick.
We- We gotta- We gotta- Okay.
This is it.
It's happening.
Holy shit.
Reduces the spread of a spell as well.
I have that too.
Pentagon?
No.
Let's throw these away.
That away.
Uh, maybe even...
That one.
So, I'm gonna be ma- Maybe the- Oh, maybe the ping pong is messing it up.
Maybe this one is also messing it up?
Wait a minute.
Oh!
Okay, so it's definitely doing something nice there.
Where's the other one I had?
What did I just- Oh, here.
I like that it's slower.
You know, that makes it go really close to me.
This is the setup.
But if I remove this, it's like the same.
But with this, it's like- It lasts a little longer, you know, in case I need to absorb it.
That's cool.
We will be making a healing wand here.
There we go.
That wand goes in here.
And then, in this first spot, we're gonna store some healing, I guess.
Man, I wish I had more storage space.
Imagine a perk that said, you can store it five times as many spells.
You know, just have five rows of these instead.
That would be awesome.
But I guess I could just put them here for now.
I mean, pick them up later, you know?
But I wanna put them in a neat pile.
Yeah, something like that.
That looks good.
Let me just quickly do this.
Neat pile of healing there, for later.
I can put these up here for now.
And I guess I can...
Uh, let's see.
Put this one there.
This wand right here?
You know, I could use this as a storage wand.
That's actually not a bad idea.
No, that's annoying.
I'm gonna have to pick it up every time.
Never mind, never mind, never mind.
I'm gonna leave this wand here.
Put it there.
Weirdly, they rotate.
I don't understand that system there.
But it is what it is.
Now we have a healing, we have a black hole.
And...
Wait, what was my original...
Was this my original...
uh, lightning wand?
Which one was my wand for lightning?
Wait.
Wait a minute, which one was my original...
I'm so confused, I'm missing a wand.
Is it the one I just left behind?
Hold on, what did I pick up?
I picked up the third wand just before, didn't I?
I picked up...
I picked up this wand and replaced it with...
Which one did I...
Well, I guess I just left it behind.
Let's go grab it.
That's kind of annoying, though.
Oh no, no, I had it here, I had it here, I understand, I understand.
This was my teleport, I think.
And then...
I'm gonna have to come back here, I guess, but that's okay.
That's fine.
Let me put some stuff here.
Right there.
This is all the healing stuff.
I'll come back for that.
There we go.
Yeah.
Then we go grab that wand we had.
And come back.
So we go down...
Oh wait, wait, wait, wait.
There we go.
Good.
That's the wrong way.
Here?
No, wait, this is the wrong way.
I think I came from...
Nope, definitely not.
Shit.
Was it through here?
Oh, I'm already lost, dude.
I think it was.
And down here.
Oh no, no, no, definitely not down there.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ah, come on.
Shit, I'm lost!
It was maybe to the right, over here.
Let's see.
This looks more promising.
I need the big red flower.
No, this is definitely not it either.
No, it's not over here.
Because I came from the bottom left, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I remember saying up and right.
Hold on.
Back to the surface.
I was up here.
Wait a minute, what's this?
Oh wait!
So this is the entrance.
I came from the left, I think.
What if I go down here?
Is it over here?
Here it is, here it is.
The big red flower.
That's what I was looking for.
Let me go down.
Left.
Want.
Beautiful.
Beautiful potato right there.
Nice.
And then I go back up.
Although, I don't need to go back up right now.
I'm fine.
This is a good setup.
At least for now, until I find something better.
Let's find some hearts, huh?
Oh, I feel...
Oh, that's awesome, man.
I feel completely invigorated here.
Finding those healing things?
Oh, and figuring out how to finally make them heal me.
What a feeling.
Now I want to explore every square inch.
Go this way.
Ah, shit, I already washed that way.
Yeah, good thing.
I should be using teleport more.
Look how efficient that is.
It's just a little bit scary to use, right?
Why did that just explode when I entered the area?
Spiders!
And we got falling fire.
Let's see, am I...
I'm not immune, okay.
I was trying to see if my shield actually...
So now I know, now I know.
The worm is going to come out of there, no?
Or is he going to burn alive?
Worm?
Oh, so burning them doesn't emit a worm.
That's cool.
Good to know.
Why does that thing look alive to me?
I guess it is.
It's a plant.
Is that from oxygen?
It is.
Health!
What's going on here?
Why is there so much flamoxia?
That thing is going to explode, right?
Let me just get rid of it.
Oh no, it's not.
Oh wait, speaking of mushrooms.
If I find some...
I think I saw some earlier here.
I'll be eating it.
Because I got to trip some balls here.
Get to the bottom of that whole mystery.
Stop shooting those.
It's not appreciated.
I knew that would happen.
I'm starting to play a little bit more loosely with the rules now that I have the healing.
But I shouldn't do that.
I'm going to stick to my original training regiment.
Another Kivaskivi.
Can I get through here?
Hey!
The magic bolt is actually doing some proper digging here.
It's not bad.
It's not bad at all.
A bunch of chaos is going on there.
We have a wand.
I wish the recoil wasn't as big though on these magic missiles.
That's a sick wand as well.
Even though it only has three, that's the only shitty part.
What was that sound?
Pachauda!
God damn.
Limbs everywhere.
This thing really breaks them apart.
At an almost molecular level here.
So hard to aim because of the recoil.
Hey!
It's crazy how good this wand is and it's just one spell, dude.
Oh!
A worm!
I'm scared of the worm.
There's the portal.
Whoa!
What's up, man?
What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Do I have worm pheromone?
I need to test the worm stuff.
Maybe I'll leave him alive.
I kind of like these making tunnels everywhere.
In fact, that pleases me.
I'm pleased.
I'm going to call him...
No, it's actually a she.
I can tell.
That is definitely Amanda.
Amanda the worm.
Man, she's been busy over here as well, huh?
Is he...
Bro, don't follow me.
Don't not follow me.
Shit.
What is that in there?
Meat.
The magic missile is great.
I've been sleeping on that spell, I think.
Kiva Skibi?
Do you want to go take care of that plant for me?
Oh, shit.
I hate the recoil on the magic missile.
That's the only downside.
It's wild.
Like, I get thrown around.
Hey, Amanda!
No!
I just hurt myself.
They killed Amanda!
Those bastards.
All's on poisons.
Get in the blood.
I need to calm down here.
Things are getting out of hand.
Just wait for him to come here.
And then we say hello.
I feel like we have a real chemistry, you know?
There's an electricity between us.
Grab the water.
Wait!
The portal is gone!
Amanda!
She must have...
She must have emptied the teleportation.
That's fine.
I wasn't intending to leave anyway.
Not yet, at least.
Hello!
I hate that they poisoned me!
I am taking way too much damage.
The problem with the first wand I have here is the range.
This one is too slow to shoot as well and too much recoil.
Like I have a good short range and a shitty long range, basically.
I can only shoot once, one at a time.
Because otherwise I will miss the next one because of the recoil.
I've been here.
So let me go left.
What was in here?
Spider?
That one?
I see you.
Thank you.
I'm getting up there in money.
Oh, not this guy.
Three shots is what he needs.
That is a lot.
Oh, wait.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Fuck, no, fuck, no.
The clouds are in there!
I'm stuck here.
Are you coming towards me?
Oh, he is.
Got him!
I think.
I hate him.
Phlomoxium, get rid of that, don't want it.
Holy shit, let me go down here.
Dude, Amanda has been at work.
Whoops.
Oh!
What?
Exquisite me?
Oh, I'm stuck!
That was brutal.
That was stupid of me.
I did not even consider that jumping in that liquid would teleport me.
Why did I not consider that?
That's the question we should be asking ourselves.
Or I should be asking myself.
That was a funny death, though.
Holy crap.
Hold on, I gotta change, we gotta update the death counter.
Let's see.
That's number 56 right there.
I mean, it's not that I'm playing to get a win here anymore.
I'm just...
I'm playing to explore.
God damn it, man.
That was such a good run, though.
Right?
That was a great run.
Wow.
That went from 0 to 100 in milliseconds.
Was not ready for that.
Okay.
Hemisphere it is.
We got blown up and sent back to the hemisphere.
Toxic rock.
I wonder what causes that, other than just random generation.
Maybe there is some kind of mix or...
combination of circumstances that can happen in this game that will produce that.
We've got a shotty man.
Got him.
Hemisphere, look at the whole family.
Also, that is acid.
Hey, guys.
Did I guess it?
No!
Okay, I hit myself.
That was a bit of a karma there.
I understand.
Totally fine.
That was evil.
I shouldn't have poured acid on them.
I was punished for my transgressions there.
And that Hemisphere hit me in the face, too.
Just jumped straight into me.
Eh?
Nice.
Getting a good amount of gold already.
Hello.
I want to find more of those oil secrets.
Ah, shit.
No, it's acid!
Wait, does acid...
Hold on.
Does acid remove poison?
It seems dumb, but I think that's what just happened.
I acid it myself and the poison went away.
I really need to find water.
I can't let this stand, you know?
This aggression from the world.
Show me the water.
That's oil.
Hemisphere.
Oh, it's stuck in there.
I freed it from its pain.
I don't know if I've seen water.
Let's check up here.
Okay, that's the entrance.
Okay.
220 gold already, that's a great start.
Here we go.
Let's empty this.
Uh...
What?
My potion is now flammable gas?
I didn't even know you could have flammable gas in your potion.
What the hell?
That's weird.
I have no idea how all that acid got replaced.
Very interesting.
Porta?
Hemis?
Aha!
They're gonna kill each other.
Oh!
And me, it seems.
Whoa!
Ow!
Wow.
Jesus.
Come here.
See ya.
300 already?
Damn.
Wait, where's all that oil going?
It's being drained.
Nice.
Collapsed mines.
I don't want to explore that, I don't think.
I already have good amounts of money.
This is good.
I'm lazy.
Whoa!
Uh-oh.
Hurry, hurry.
Don't get hit by the falling fire!
Come here.
Look at that little.
Ah.
So many hortas.
And there's a wand.
Very good.
It's what I've been looking for.
Oh, it's a trap.
I'm gonna get through there.
Oh, that's so cool.
It's all gonna catch fire.
Ha ha ha.
Like when that thing spreads out, one of the coolest animations.
Here we go.
Lights and eggs.
That is actually something I need.
Well, not the eggs, but the light.
To explore the dark place.
Let's grab some water.
There we go.
How are you not that...
What the fuck?
I hit you like a million times.
Stupid dog.
Ah.
Oh no, my... oh my god.
I'm dying.
Come on, please.
Phew.
Okay.
Jesus.
Just give me one more wand.
Wait, where was that wand?
I completely forgot about the wand.
No wait, I took the wand.
I'm an idiot.
It's because there was nothing really...
Let me try it.
Where's the light?
The light is a lie.
Oh, it's shuffle.
But...
At some point it'll give me light.
Maybe.
No light today.
The whole gang is there.
I'm gonna die.
I want HP.
Okay, I guess we go through portal.
No more fucking around.
This is it.
Don't even hit a single pixel.
Phew.
Okay, get away from that fire.
Don't know what just happened there.
We just got out of there.
That was so close.
Okay.
Let's see here.
Nope.
Aha!
Black holes.
And what do we have here?
Wait, no wand tinkering?
Wands cannot be tinkered with, but enemies may drop blood money.
That sounds...
Unbelievably bad.
How the fuck is this a perk?
And not the other thing, or the opposite thing of a perk?
Faster projectiles?
Fly fa...
Ooh, that's not bad.
Spontaneous generation.
Vomit near you evolves into helpful red minions.
Nah.
Imma reroll that one, boy.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
That costs money.
This is...
Oh, wait a minute.
Do I even have anything proper to fight with?
This wand is not bad.
In itself.
I think I...
If I buy anything, it should be this one.
Just because it has some nice damage on it.
Or that one.
No, that's a shuffle.
Um...
I can always get this later.
I'm gonna buy this.
I'm gonna buy it.
I can always come back here and do this again, so...
That's fine.
It cast four spells, though.
So that's not great.
That means it's gonna cast this one, which is those two.
One, two, three.
Actually, maybe it is great.
Oh!
Does this hurt me?
It does not.
Okay, good to know.
But the mana charge speed is a bit terrible.
Don't know if I like that.
Oh my god.
Mana charge speed ten?
Yikes.
I don't understand these.
Someone's an otherwise empty egg that casts a spell upon cracking open.
Unless it simply means...
Have I been misunderstanding this in the entire time?
Let's say we do this.
Uh, this...
Will that actually just shoot that when it breaks open?
Okay, but why is it not a modifier, then?
Well, I guess because it's a projectile.
Itself.
Okay, that's weird.
That's what threw me off so long.
I get it now.
I get it.
So, you know what would be cool with this hollow egg?
You could put in, let's say, a holy hand grenade.
Right?
You can throw this and be at a much safer distance.
You know?
Because it will only throw the holy hand grenade when this breaks open.
Not bad.
You can get into, you can let it, you know, fall into a tight corridor and just fall down a tube or something and then explode at the end.
I see the use.
I see it now.
Weirdly, there's still no light on that egg.
Isn't that weird?
How much damage does this even do?
Let's see.
Fifty.
Sixty.
Wait, thirty?
Oh, it's mega random.
I guess this depends on how many of these follow-ups are gonna actually hit anything.
Well, with this one,
maybe better, but the charge speed is just so bad.
It's so bad.
Get rid of that.
How about we just do this?
No, I run out of mana on that too.
What if we just do this on this one?
It's better.
But it's not, oh my god, the mana charge on that is even worse!
This is horrible.
These are absolutely terrible.
Yeah, I'm not sure I like any of this.
I do like the black hole though, so I will grab that later.
But for now, let's get out of here.
We can...
I don't even know.
Yeah, no, put this here, I guess.
Because if I'm not gonna use it now, I can at least have it up here and I can replace this wand, right?
That's how I should be thinking about it.
Let's put this here and we replace this wand.
In fact, I'm just gonna throw these wands away.
Nobody wants them.
No, wait, wrong wand.
That goes there.
This one also gets thrown away.
There.
That's what we got.
Let's go.
A terrible start, to be honest.
But it is what it is.
It's already out of mana, it's wild.
Oh, whoa, be careful.
It's weird how when you're standing on things, you still sort of kick them.
Oh god, no, stop.
I was hit for like the smallest amount ever.
Where are you?
I saw a shotgun man.
Got a recharge or wand.
It works.
Didn't.
I need to find another lightning bolt.
There's so many wands I can't get to probably because I don't have any digging.
Oh, that sucks.
Shit.
Let there be digging wands for me, please.
I do be needing it.
Do not get hit by that.
Actually, it's not going terribly right now.
All things considered.
It's so weird going from having a teleport wand to not having one.
You get so immediately used to it.
Wow.
That was the craziest shot.
I killed this guy, it bounced off and hit this guy over here as well.
I think he hit himself.
Or something.
Did not go according to plan, that's for sure.
Shit.
Nice.
Slime comes to the rescue.
How are you not dead?
Oh, I was using the wrong wand.
That's why.
I was using my normal-ass wand.
I'm tempted to go through.
Sounds a little bit nuts, but...
Nah, I still have ADHD, should be fine.
But how am I going to get around?
I can't go anywhere.
Seems like everything is blocked off.
Let me go up and left.
I think I saw something there.
Or actually here.
Yes, here we go.
Grab some more water.
Okay, so that's a dead end as well.
That's blocked off.
Shit, I can't get anywhere.
Am I actually locked off from the entire place here?
There's no way.
This level is actually locked off to me!
Have I not been everywhere in this level so far?
Like, I've explored every nook that I can go to.
Am I losing it?
Hold on.
There was nothing else over here, right?
Fuck!
Okay,
well, I guess we've got to go through a portal.
I actually cannot get anywhere else in this level.
That is wild, I've never seen that.
There's stuff, I think, in there.
Shit, I didn't have any more teleporting.
Or not teleporting, levitation.
No, that's not what it's called either, it's just called levitation.
That's the word.
It's probably what they would say in Italy.
But I don't know.
Ah, wait, wait, wait!
No, I can't go here either.
Yeah, this is actually insane, I can't go anywhere.
We're in!
It is what it is.
I will take this.
See, that's nice.
Circle of vigor.
That's a good start right there.
What's that?
Circle of displacement?
I don't know what that means.
Reduce spread is good.
Let's see the perks.
More hatred.
Stainless armor again.
And close call.
I'm tempted to just take this one again, because it's actually just good.
Right?
There's no reason not to take that.
It's a good one.
It is.
But I still don't really have any damage.
That's the problem.
This one is 50 off, and that's actually a decent spell.
This one with this one could be nice.
Right?
Reduce spread on it.
But this one is 140.
At least this was like, what is that?
108.
It's not enough for both.
But I can come back.
As long as I can dig.
And I can dig with this, with the Trippical Bolt.
Okay.
That's not bad, that's not bad.
I'm going to go with that.
And that.
Now I kind of regret throwing away my other wands.
Why did I do that?
God damn it.
I make stupid decisions right now.
It's wild.
I'm going to put this here.
And then in the second one, we're just going to simply...
How much mana is this?
One?
We can just put some light in here.
Why not?
For now at least.
And then in that one...
Let me see.
It does, what is it?
Five damage each?
Maybe that's not too great either.
Maybe I just still want to have this.
Then I have to, I guess...
Do this in the next area.
Because I need damage, this is not going to be enough.
All... Maybe I find damage down there.
And then I do this.
As an emergency type deal.
That's not bad.
We have 50 left, I can't buy anything else.
Definitely going to come back here for more of those spells.
I'm going to take stainless armor.
Yeah.
Ah, there's a wand.
Are we lucky?
Hold on, there's gold.
The gold has disappeared.
It's just gone.
Should have thought about the mana on that one.
Not that I had much choice.
Can I not just go around here?
God, I hate having low mana.
Please.
Short range homing.
I mean, all right.
God, man.
It's going to be a struggle to get through this level.
Man, what's up with the wands here?
Yes.
Sure.
Triple, triple, that's not bad at all.
And this wand right here is not too terrible either.
This digs.
Doesn't it?
Wait, it docked way more last time I used this.
What's the difference?
Oh, but it's definitely digging.
It's doing a good amount of digging.
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick.
What are all the wands I'm being blessed with here?
So lesson learned, do not walk into these.
Can I destroy them?
Let's just get... I gotta wait.
Come on.
There we go.
And not... a homing.
With a summon egg.
God damn.
Hmm.
I think homing is better than short-range homing.
Right.
Man, I drained 70, 40.
Okay.
I think I want that instead.
Can I find...
Oh!
That thing's gonna go boom-boom.
Do it.
There it is.
I really just want to find a lightning bolt wand.
I feel like it's very common to find down here.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ah, actually I don't want to tangle with that dude.
Or that dude.
I actually don't have any firepower at all.
Wait, summon's an egg that houses a friendly creature.
Wait, that didn't... I didn't... I thought it was just one of those hollow eggs.
Let's try it.
Is that killing something down there?
Hey, horta!
Hey, what's up, people?
Help me, help me.
Release the army!
Kill for me, people!
They're not doing shit!
And they're on fire, and they're on top of me.
This is actually bad.
I just can't kill that cannon.
I don't have the damage.
It's wild, I can't.
Come on, army.
Don't run into me when you're burning.
Oh, please, please stop, please stop.
Ah, this is over, man.
I have no firepower.
Release!
Oh, it's empty.
Okay.
I just gotta wander around and look for a wand.
That is my objective.
An amazing wand, mind you.
Dead end here.
Oh, god.
This is a mess.
At least my creatures are helping a lot here.
They're doing work.
Get him, get him!
Yes!
The slime guy is very nice.
Oh, my god!
The artillery.
I can't, I can't!
Hey, you like these?
Oh, I'm stuck in here, man.
This is bad.
Oh, it's fucking over!
It's so over!
Oh, my god, it's over!
Dig!
Get him!
Yes!
Good, good, good, good, good, good.
No, we gotta find a portal right now.
I'm just gonna dig down.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
These are the worst wands I've ever had in my life.
Uh, just dig, just dig.
We're digging.
No, no, no.
Don't come down here.
Oh, shit!
I'm stuck, I'm stuck.
The ice is freezing.
The water's freezing, I mean.
Oh, two!
I swear, this is all a mess.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not happening that way.
Come on, portal.
Any off-screen shot right now and I'm dead.
Like that.
Oh, my god.
I am fighting for my life.
Tell me it's down there.
Nope.
It is not.
Whoo!
Nice, nice, nice.
What is down here?
Blood.
Oh, I hear, I hear it!
It's right below me, it's right below me.
Shit, there's one of those things there.
I don't like that at all.
That is a disaster.
Nope, I have to go left.
We're digging.
Come on.
Dig for me.
Okay, okay.
Wait, what?
I just found something!
I just fucking remembered I have healing.
Oh, my god.
I have nothing to say.
I have no words.
No words required.
What is this I'm hearing?
You hear that?
It's like right here.
Am I crazy?
There's something going on down there.
Ah, I hurt myself.
What is that?
Hold on.
I hurt myself again because of these goddamn pollen!
Okay, this water is annoying me.
We gotta drain it.
There we go.
Drain that shit.
Is that just the sound of the...
Huh?
What?
Okay, I hear the portal here, but listen here.
There's some kind of... sound.
The hell is in here?
Is it there?
Wait a minute.
Is it up here?
Is it there?
Actually could...
It could be up here.
Is it in here?
Oh, my god.
Oh, fuck me.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
But what is that sound?
I'm just driving me nuts.
Fuck it.
I'm going down.
We have a portal.
I'm going.
Yeah, I'm going.
This run is rip, I think.
No matter what.
We don't even have money for most of this shit.
What's that?
Projectile energy shields.
Hook bolt.
That's like the formation behind your back.
Let's see the perks.
Revenge tentacle.
I don't like that.
Exploding gold.
Gold dropped by enemies, explodes when it disappears.
Is picked up or touched by other enemies?
No.
An angry spirit comes to your aid.
Copying nearby spells.
No, I'm going to spend my money on reroll.
Living on the hitch?
No.
Phasing?
What?
Saving grace.
If you would die and have more than one HP, your HP sets a... Bro.
Huh?
Isn't this... Phasing sounds OP as fuck?
How is this not just immunity to most damage?
What the hell?
Dang.
If you would die and have more than one HP.
I think I want saving grace.
I mean, how can you not take that?
So, I wonder if this means...
Let's say I die.
I now have one HP.
Then I heal.
And then I die again.
And now I have one HP again.
Like, it just keeps going, right?
As long as I have more than one HP.
I'm taking it.
Can't buy any of this shit.
So, I'm going to go into the next level with absolutely nothing to my name and I'm going to die immediately.
That's the unfortunate truth.
In fact, no, no, no.
Let's heal first.
I'm banking on finding something in the next level here.
There we go.
I need to find some kind of weapon.
Oh, put these here.
These ones?
No, I hate these ones.
Absolutely terrible.
Homing?
Let's try and see if we can make something at least a little sweet before we move on with what I've got here.
How about homing pollen?
Huh?
Triplek?
Triple spell?
One, two, three, one, two, and something else.
I don't even know.
Maybe that one.
Let's see.
That's not bad.
I like that.
But it never shoots this, it seems.
Cool.
Maybe it's better on that one.
Hmm.
Maybe one of these instead.
Why is that not being...
Oh, mana max 110.
Oh, this cost 70.
That's right.
That is a lot.
That's a lot of goddamn mana.
So maybe instead of these.
How much mana is this?
35?
Wow.
Well...
Shit!
Well, that ruins that.
How about this one?
That has shitty recharge though.
The charge speed is really great on this one.
Can I use that to my advantage?
That's what I'm thinking.
Somehow.
This one has a lot of mana, but it's very slow charge and shuffle.
Hmm.
What if I just keep it simple here?
Let's just say we do a homing triple.
One, two, three.
These cost 10 mana each, right?
So that's 100 mana.
And this one has 110 mana max.
So we could do one more.
But it's not going to be in the same shot then.
It's going to be a little annoying.
Yeah, then it shoots one.
No, that's bad.
This is better.
That's not bad.
That's like acceptable, I would say.
You know, it could be better, but...
It is what it is.
What if I do this?
Am I crazy?
That is faster.
I'm not sure.
I feel like it is.
It only costs 2 mana.
Let's put it in.
Um, triplicate, put there.
Triple spell there.
Healing is good.
Now in this one, let's put some bombs.
Why the hell not?
And in the first one...
Hmm.
I do not know.
Maybe we still need that just basic thing.
It's good to have, I guess.
With some light, why not?
That seems like an okay thing.
Let's go!
We are now in the easy base, and all we have is Poland.
What's up, people?
Oh, there's a wand.
Let's see.
Do I get lucky?
Please.
What the hell is this?
Oh, I like damage plus.
That's nice.
Quadruple spell.
Formation above and below.
Cast 3 spells above.
No, large spirit bolt.
Damage field.
Gives a projectile and energy field that constantly deals 3 point...
Whoa!
Let's try this.
Let's see what this does.
Oh, okay.
Does this damage me, though?
No, spirit bolt is...
Ooh!
Do I get hurt by that?
Just, just, just, just, just... Okay.
So wait, it shoots...
Ahead.
Wait, it doesn't shoot ahead.
What the fuck?
That does not shoot ahead at all.
Wait a minute.
Oh, these are modifiers.
Weird.
Cast 3 spells.
1, 2, 3.
Oh, but it's a quadruple, so it casts this one.
Which is 1, 2, 3.
That one, and then...
I guess 2 more?
Very confusing.
But I like it.
I like this.
I like it more than this.
Useless wand.
I still... I kind of want to try it.
Oh, I wasn't ready.
I wasn't ready, bastard.
Yo, it's actually really good at shooting around corners.
I'm just scared of this because it can hurt me.
Oh, God.
It's actually not that great.
Oh, my God!
It's terrible.
Guys, I'm dead.
I can't kill enemies.
I have literally zero firepower.
It's over.
It's actually over.
I need to find wands.
Immediately.
Unless...
Come here.
Why am I so... Oh, it's the oil.
Oh, that's so annoying.
Come here.
Stand next to me.
Hey, I'm right here.
You know you see me.
Oh, my God.
Let me resort back to my...
No, that does no damage.
Let's try this one again.
Fuck!
Wrong wand!
Get in there!
Oh, this is terrible!
Oh, my God!
I need to get close.
Hey, that actually works, sort of.
Yeah!
Okay, I'm now melee.
I'm a melee mage.
That's how I do things.
Actually, sort of works.
Oh!
Wow.
Let's not go that way.
Does this dig at all?
Let's do anything.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
And this relaxing music as well.
While I'm getting my ass handed to me.
It's actually not bad.
This wand here.
This messed up wand.
I just need enemies to get close to me.
Come here.
Actually, I can still do this towards these guys.
Stop!
Wrong wand again, man!
I hate it.
It's over.
Hey, you like that?
You like this?
Come here.
Oh, my God, this wand is terrible.
Can I operate this gun?
I'm surrounded.
I'm fucking dead!
This is the worst run ever!
Yeah, I'm about to die here.
I have one HP.
Oh, I used all my healing by accident.
Just, you know what?
Fucking kill me.
I can't take it anymore.
Nope, we're starting over.
That is some bullshit.
Nope!
I am not continuing under these goddamn conditions.
I am not... okay.
We gotta have a new rule.
You can't move on when you don't have proper wands.
Even though you have one HP.
You have to keep exploring.
Because it's just impossible to kill anything if you don't have a wand.
You know?
So that's the new rule.
No more when you have a certain amount of money you go through the portal.
No, when you have a good enough wand.
No matter what.
Then you go through the portal.
That's the new rule.
And we're sticking to it.
Even if we're at one HP.
If we die, we die.
You know?
Oh, let me also quickly update.
That's 57.
There we go.
Hello.
Good old Barney.
In the hemisphere.
The hell?
I thought that was a bat for a second.
That's just a wild TNT.
There's a himis.
Sweet.
Now that's going well.
That was a bit too risky.
If I hear the cocking of the shotgun, you just gotta get out of there.
Don't commit.
Bad idea.
Uh-oh.
There's water down here.
If I can lure him down here, that would be grand.
Also, speak enough.
Brine!
That is just water.
Come here, come here, come here, come here.
Yeah, look at me!
Look at me!
Come here!
Lovely.
That is lovely.
That is grand.
Man, this is a perfect game so far.
You know how they say money can't buy happiness?
That's not true in Neuter.
Money can definitely buy you wands, and healing, and good health.
Everything is just money.
Money, money, money.
You need that money.
Aha!
Found a wand, yeah.
Boink!
That better make a hole big enough.
Okay, good.
That guy's gonna burn to death.
Just wait it out.
I'm sure the hymns meanwhile.
Is he not burning?
He's not taking damage it seems.
I died, good.
Wand for me!
What is that?
Look at this!
Doesn't that look like a man with a fiery peg of a leg?
Or for a leg?
Sure, thanks.
I can dig with this.
What do we have here?
Chaotic polymorphine?
Thank you.
Wow!
How did I not get hit?
Incredible.
Whoa!
Show thyself?
Dude, it's going phenomenal.
Why is everything shaking so much?
I guess explosions are happening off screen somewhere.
But a lot of them.
Another wand.
Sure.
Thank you.
Ah, ooh, okay, hold on.
That's what's going on.
Oh!
There's a worm!
Oh crap.
Uh oh.
Thank you.
I'm gonna grab that wand.
Rain cloud?
Um, let's see.
0.03, 0.42.
Is that 220?
It's... I'm not sure.
Ooh!
That wand is really nice.
Even though it's shuffle, you know.
Do I want rain?
I think I want rain.
Rain is cool.
So Amanda's been at it again here.
Whoopsie.
That's what caused all the... Oh, that's lava.
Don't fall down there.
Don't go through yet.
We're not done.
Definitely not done.
What's going on there?
Oh, Amanda died!
Worm blood.
Kinda wanna try and drink it.
Said nobody ever.
Except me.
Oh!
I hate poison.
Wait, what?
What, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what?
You're seeing things more clearly.
Coss ingesting worm blood?
Oh yeah, my screen is all weird.
Wait, what?
What am I seeing more clearly?
What, I...
I don't get it.
I saw the colors change for sure.
What just happened?
I'm so sorry, Amanda.
I drank your blood.
I see things clearly now.
Man, this looks exactly like that other spot I just bombed.
Oh, it's stuck at the wall!
Most perfect bomb ever.
Gold.
Good.
400 gold.
I thought that was gonna catch fire.
Collapsed mines.
They don't seem very co...
I guess nothing specially collapsed about this place.
That I can see at least.
Where is the collapse?
Ah, all this poison is just pissing me off.
It's bleeding it everywhere!
There we go.
I wish I had a perk that would make me bleed, or not bleed, just emit water everywhere I go.
Imagine that one.
Just automatically turn everything into water.
If it's toxic, you know?
In fact, let me grab my water bottle and fill it up.
I'm grabbing it.
Imagine the clothes after being in oil.
Must be the worst.
Here we've got the roots of the world tree.
In fact, I'm gonna call it the all tree.
It just seems like such an important...
Oh, here we are.
We don't have any light.
No light.
Shit.
That place is so mysterious.
Such a hard place to reach too, because you gotta get back through the levels up here.
After finding a light.
Wait, what, what, what do I have?
Alright, I have this.
I got him.
There's a frog!
Ah, this guy is dangerous.
Shit, how am I missing so much?
Get out of there!
Oh, no.
Don't follow me!
Run!
No!
That is scary.
Maybe now it's time to go through the portal.
Although...
Yeah.
Let's just go.
We have 500 monies.
That's quite a lot.
Let's see what we have.
Homebringer, I think.
What is that?
I think that's Energy Sphere?
Yeah, Energy Sphere.
Horrible mana charge speed.
Nope.
Oh!
And nice teleport.
And one of those, okay.
Concentrated spells.
Greed.
Protectile slower.
Uh...
Hmm.
Oh, wait a minute!
Did I have this one before and is that what caused the black hole to be slow?
That could actually be it.
I remember having some kind of field around me at that time.
Unless I'm remembering wrong there.
I think I like this.
This is like a solid one.
You know?
Lower spread.
It actually says extra damage too.
I didn't even realize.
I was just taking this for the lower spread because I hate spread.
But that's awesome.
How much extra damage are we talking?
I mean, we have some...
This is a terrible wand.
This is a shuffle, but we kind of need it.
Because there's teleport.
Take it.
We don't need this many though.
Get rid of those.
That looks funny.
It looks like it's like a lower res of this one.
Isn't that weird?
Uh, okay.
I could go with saw blades.
Those are quite nice.
Oh, actually there's a light.
But I need something...
I would need to be able to shoot something that is...
What do you call it?
Uh, like the rock, you know?
Infinite rocks.
Because the rock doesn't disappear and the light stays.
So if I can just shoot rocks everywhere, I can have lights everywhere.
But I was trying to think of other spells that would do something similar.
I guess I could just have a wand that shoots fast and just spam it everywhere.
And that would light things up for me.
That could be an option.
So...
Let's take this one.
Replace it.
Replace this one.
And then...
These are the small ones, right?
Just to confirm?
Yeah.
I have such a hard time telling between them for some reason.
I bet if I saw them next to each other, I wouldn't have trouble, but...
I like it.
Not bad.
But...
We could also use them with the...
I think it's a spitter bolt or energy sphere.
Grab that one.
It's even cheaper.
That's weird.
Energy sphere with timer.
Man, the game really loves the timers, huh?
And then...
It's actually five spells per cast.
Yikes.
Don't like that.
This does five damage.
This does twenty.
Hmm...
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
If this casts five per...
This could be a nice nuker.
You know?
Just go like...
If someone's really close...
You hit them for like a lot of damage.
Like, check this out.
Wait, wait, wait.
How does that make sense?
Twenty, forty, sixty, eighty, a hundred.
Oh, wait, is it this one, I guess?
Extra damage?
So what, it adds...
How much?
That's like...
One hundred and fifty percent extra damage?
There's no way.
Weird.
That's a lot of damage.
That's a nice nuker wand right there.
And the charge speed is slow, but it is what it is.
You know, you shoot a couple, you don't shoot it all the time.
You shoot it sometimes.
And then for normal damage, we have this.
There and there.
Let's just see.
Whoa!
Uh...
Wait, wait, wait.
Why does that do so much damage?
Hold on.
Oh, I can test this.
So this is three damage.
Sixteen?
What?
This perk is nuts!
Oh, wait, lower spread?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
If I put this here...
There's no spread!
Oh, my God.
Uh, it cast five spells.
One, which is dong dong.
Dong dong, three, four...
Oh, uh...
Okay, that doesn't have to actually do much more than I thought.
Maybe this is better.
Like, that's two, that's...
Shall we do that?
That's insane.
But...
I still don't like it.
It's the timer that throws me off.
The energy sphere with timer really messes with me.
It's just such a weird mechanic that I just never...
I don't like it.
I don't like it at all.
We have bombs.
Do we have anything else?
I can't use this, unfortunately.
I think I'm just gonna rock the spark bolt, man.
Like, it's doing good damage.
You know, it's not bad.
It's actually wild.
Or
unless...
Oh, it's because I'm a low mana, it does that.
No, I just want this.
It's a little pathetic, but it's definitely enough for the next level.
And then we have the nuker.
That shoots all these five at the same time.
This is a sick nuke.
Boink!
That's a one-shot on most things.
Yeah, this is great.
Yes, sir.
But here's the thing.
180...
Yeah, this is fine.
We leave.
But I'll take these with me.
Now let's heal.
Heal up, and we go.
This one looks like a chandelier.
I wonder if the want the signs are also randomized.
Because they seem random.
Bro, the concentrated spells perk is wild.
Look at that!
That's a spark bolt, damn it.
It's insane.
We have full water?
Oh, look at all this gold, though.
Volcanic rock.
We can't do any digging.
That's the bad thing about this setup here.
I just realized, I should have put...
Oh, I had a fire bolt somewhere, didn't I?
I should have put that in one of the wands.
Shit.
Forgot about it.
It happens.
I cannot hit.
That was a full shot to the face!
Oh my god, again!
That guy's a menace!
Damn!
Got my ass kicked.
That's fair play there.
I sucked.
I didn't dodge that properly.
What is that?
Oh, gold, nice.
Oh, there's a little hole here.
Oh my god.
Stop with the fireworks.
Whoo!
Here, we're gonna nuke.
Ah!
There we go.
In fact, I may just use this as my main weapon.
It's so good.
But if this bounces off somewhere and hits me, then I'm instantly dead.
That's the only...
Ooh, what do we have there?
Damn.
Wait, tail of fire on TNT?
Isn't that kind of irresponsible?
Let's try it, man.
I likey very muchy.
That is awesome.
That's my digging wand.
I kind of want to just blow everything up now.
Oh wait, it's shooting...
Wasn't that shooting two at a time?
That was so weird.
76 crit from a...
Oh!
From a single spark bolt.
Oh my god, are you actually kidding me?
Like, it was safe and then this bullshit fell down and I got caught on fire again.
I'm so unlucky.
Oh my god, don't drop that on me.
Ah!
Shit.
This game is pain sometimes, dude.
Pure pain.
That's a wand.
Maybe I get lucky.
I can definitely get in there.
Oh ho!
Okay, those are the big ones.
Yeah, okay, it's not that hard to tell actually.
Ah ha.
I don't like that.
It's too scary.
Nope.
I am scared.
200 monies?
Man, I don't have a lot.
Mix it up, come on.
What the hell is going on over there?
Sounded like that one scene from Lord of the Rings.
Where the bucket falls down the well and makes a giant noise.
Things just keep falling here.
Look at that giant mountain of coal.
Now that's a coal mine.
And the coal is a mine.
A mine.
Order that.
Everything's on fire now.
Set down here.
Portal is there.
Another one right next to it.
Wow.
Actually, they always tend to be right next to each other.
I can't wait to make a map of this.
Dude, I'm going to be mapping the shit out of this.
Next time I'm going to be drawing things.
I may actually draw a little bit before next time.
Let me destroy that.
Oh!
That was a potion inside.
I see.
But I guess you can't really map like in detail because it's randomized.
But you can sort of map general layout of things.
You know, like this place is always below the hemisphere.
I checked this one already, yeah.
In fact, all the levels here are actually just sort of stacked on top of each other.
At least that's what it feels like.
And then they're also, I think, kind of squarish or like rectangle-ish.
Based on just the layout and the limits of the level, you know?
So you can make a rough drawing, I guess.
Portal there.
Okay.
Go up and left.
Man, I'm so sad I died in that run because I took the teleportation, man.
And you know what the funny thing is?
If I had played a little bit more safe beforehand and not lost so much HP after I healed up, I probably could have survived down there as well and recovered.
It was all like, it all snowballed into that result, you know, because I wasn't being careful to begin with.
And that's sad.
But it's another lesson learned, even though you find a lot of healing.
Don't start getting cocky, you know?
Don't just play like normal.
Because that's totally what happened.
I found all that healing and was like, ah!
Go kill everything!
I have no care in the world because I can heal, you know?
Didn't matter.
As soon as you start to let down your guard, man, that's when the game slaps you in the face.
And it's like, hey, listen up!
You're still playing Neuter, you hear me?
Now sit down.
Pay attention.
I'm just imagining being tied to a chair and some guy standing there, like, slapping me, you know?
Listen up.
Don't fall asleep.
Come on, man.
Give me some hearts here.
What is happening?
I need health, dude.
Otherwise, I can't survive.
I need a lot of it.
I'm hearing gongs.
Why am I hearing gongs?
And the saw blade is amazing.
Aha!
The fungal caverns!
Oh, my God!
I know what time it is.
What is that?
What is that material down there?
Ooh, let's not do that.
Don't go into teleportation.
I learned my lesson, sir.
But we're going to be tripping in here, brother.
If we find some mushrooms... Oh, God.
Ooh.
A spark bolt with a trigger.
It's better than that.
That's a spark bolt with no trigger.
Let's just simply replace it.
Health, finally.
Yay!
Uh-oh.
Die.
Where's your friend?
Actually, I think I see... Is that...
Oh, yeah, there's fungus right here.
Which makes sense.
Fungal cavern.
Oh, my God.
Die, please.
What the hell?
This guy's half invisible!
Oh, this thing is spawning them.
I don't like that at all.
I'm stuck, dammit!
I don't know what's happening!
There's something wrong with my character!
What the fuck is going on?!
There... I think I was confused or something on my character.
I don't know what was happening.
I could not control it.
What the fuck just happened?
When I tried to go up, it didn't want to go up.
When I went right, it went left.
I have no idea what just happened.
What the fuck?
Shit!
Oh, what a painful death, dude.
I was just about to trip on some shrooms!
And then the shrooms tripped on me.
That's sad.
That's also sad.
Snow potion right there?
Nobody likes a snow potion.
Actually, I'm just gonna... God dammit!
Fuck!
I was hoping to get to do some of the things I had on my list today.
Oh well.
I don't have any more time, unfortunately.
That's gonna be the end for that one.
Ripped, man!
I feel like these things are gonna be on my list for the next 10 years.
This game is hard.
What can I say?
I like the amount of viewers right now.
69!
Keep it up.
You're not allowed to leave or join.
Ah, shit!
We lost it.
That was a nice amount, though.
Love the hymn is spam.
I would say I had good runs today.
And they ended in an unfortunate way.
But they were very good runs.
Making a map is a good plan.
I can't wait.
In fact, do you guys mind if I spend some time just from memory trying to make something before next time?
And then I can fill it out, sort of.
Because I have a general layout in my brain already.
And I think it would take a long time on stream.
You know, we can sort of fill it out and slowly change it and modify it as we go along.
Hey, Yuxo!
Neutte is such a great game, but very unforgiving.
Exactly.
Just like Rainworld.
I have very similar feelings about this game as I do with Rainworld.
I still want to say Rainworld is way harder.
And way more unforgiving.
But yeah, they're both incredible games.
Definitely same vibes.
The thing about Rainworld, there's actually some really amazing lore in there.
So far, I haven't really found any real lore in Neutte.
I'm starting to think it may not be there.
You know, maybe, I mean, it's obviously there somewhere, but it's not a lot.
And I don't think it's very detailed.
You know, that's my initial thought, but maybe I'll find some.
We'll have to see.
It took a while in Rainworld as well to find that lore, so, you know, could be the same situation as Rainworld.
Not that I mind.
I mean, this game is purely gameplay, right?
And that's fine.
Say you play Neutte for lore is a bit weird, I guess.
You definitely play Neutte for the gameplay, which is awesome.
Yeah, that's the feeling I get broke.
That is very hidden.
It's hidden behind stories and stories of extremely dense rock.
Oh yeah, the alchemists cite their secrets well, exactly.
They obfuscated, or whatever they called it.
For the uninitiated.
True seekers must dig deep, indeed.
Yeah, exactly.
Anyway, so, by the way, I'm sorry for not putting up a reminder for this stream yesterday.
Usually, I try to do it 24 hours beforehand.
But I wasn't planning on streaming today.
This was sort of an impromptu thing.
But something I had to do got cancelled, so I was just like, fuck yeah, it's Neutte time, baby!
So I just threw it up real quick.
That's gonna happen sometimes, just so you know.
Sometimes I just feel like playing and I go and I go do it.
Anyway, people, I'm gonna say thank you for watching.
I gotta play some... Oh, man.
Actually, I gotta eat something first, and then I'm gonna play some Prey after that.
Because that game is hooking me right now.
So thanks for watching.
I'll see you guys in the next one, alright?
Have a great Sunday, and I hope you had a fantastic weekend.
Bye-bye.